Relax... What happened?
I'm a little nervous because I haven't told anyone yet.
But is everything okay?
Okay...
It's that--
It's-- It's so intimate, to be honest, so...
You're scaring me, Val.
If it's scaring you, you wouldn't know--
You wouldn't know how I'm feeling.
Hey, but...
Look at me.
Hey.
You can trust me.
You know that?
I'm in love.
With a girl.
Lupita.
Mom!
What happened?
- We were very worried.
- You're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Well, sorry I made you worried.
Why didn't you say anything?
I just went to the hospital to thank the man that helped me.
I don't know, I just woke up feeling like it, so I went.
I didn't think you'd get worried.
Listen carefully, Lupita.
Your life isn't the same anymore. You're still in danger. You can't--
You can't just go out like that again, please.