Ugh, this door.
My girl!
- Chivis.
- Were the things I sent through Jacobo useful?
Yeah. Yeah, they were. We only came here to get some clothes for Juliana and that's it.
Well, then go ahead. I'll go get some fresh water with your friend, yes?
- Yeah. In fact, that would be nice.
- Yeah, it's okay. I'll be right there.
I'll go upstairs.
Silvina, thank you so much for lending me your house.
I did it for Valentina.
I wanted to tell you that--
Although I'm aware of what you and your mother are up to, I don't care about what happens to my house.
What does worry me is Valentina.
I don't want anything bad to happen to her.
Because she's been hanging around with you.
She's an angel.
She's always willing to help the others.
Don't take advantage of her naivety.
I'll go fetch the water.
What is it? What's up with that face?
You know what?
I think Silvina doesn't like me.
Um...
I don't think that's possible.
Silvina is surely happy you're living at her house.
- No, Val.
- What?
Silvina doesn't want me to be near you.
Wait.
Silvina is super protective. But she's super kind and super good.
But if there's someone in this world who's kinder and better, it's you.
So, believe me, that's not an option.
Val, what's up, huh?
- With what?
- You're acting so nonchalantly.
I mean, it's like you're not realizing what's happening.
Don't you think we're--
Making a mistake?
Um...
I don't-- I don't understand.
You're scaring me a little. I don't understand what's going on.
Don't you think we should give each other some space?
So each of us can think about what's happening.
So each of us can think about what we're feeling.
And then go back to our normal lives?
Well, I'm very sure of what I want and of what I'm feeling.
And let me tell you that my normal life stinks.
Okay? And that everything-- Listen to me, everything!
Is better now you're in my life.
And I want this to be my normal life.