Look at all the things Val borrowed me.
They're beautiful, she's got really good taste, hasn't she?
Look at this.
Mom?
Mom, what's up?
You're very odd.
What happened? You said you liked this place.
It's not that, honey.
It's just that lately I've been thinking a lot about Chino.
No.
Come on, mom! No.
We had agreed on that this was in the past, why are you--?
And even after all the things he's done to you. I just don't understand you!
Honestly.
Well, just--
Forget all the grudges and forgive him.
- No, but--
- Don't hate him.
What the heck is bugging you?
Why are you a mess because of Chino again?
Don't mind me.
I'm too sensitive because of all the things that's happened.
[Jacobo speaking in other languages]
So, can Chino speak three other languages?
Can he talk about finances, about numbers? Think a little, please!
I don't understand.
And you think I do?
I don't understand how I came back to life after being dead either.
Let's suppose you're not Chino.
- Where is he?
- I have no idea. And I know it's too weird for you.
Yes, I know it's weird to think that I'm in your husband's body.
That I'm talking from someone else's soul. It is just as weird to me!
Hey.
Mom.
I'm sorry.