I mean, my daughter--
My daughter Valentina kissing another girl. No, not another girl, sorry, correction.
My daughter Valentina kissing a girl who in this life is also my daughter.
No, Juliana is not your daughter, don't exaggerate.
Are you not listening to what I'm saying?
- Completely, you're exaggerating.
- Don't tell me now to grow up, Camilo, please!
21st century! 21st century, homosexuality--
I'm not talking about homosexuality, I know my daughter!
My daughter had three boyfriends, I've met them, my daughter is heterosexual.
Listen to what I'm going to say.
Three boyfriends, four or five. Whatever it is! She's not interested in men.
She's experimenting with another girl. What's the problem?
- Enough?
- Huh? What's the problem?
- Yes.
Can I speak to my friend instead of doctor Guerra?
- Completely.
- I know you don't have kids. Try to understand me! Seat here and try to understand me!
- I am trying to help you!
- Well, then help me understand.
Why everything I've done, that I thought was right, turned out it was wrong!
She's experimenting with another girl, let her be.
I don't have a problem with her experimenting, that's not the problem.
If this happens, can you imagine the mess we'll be in?