She doesn't answer and she knows she must answer me.
Then text her and say the four of us are having dinner together, and that I'll pick Juliana up.
Hey.
What's up?
I don't know. Valentina's acting very weird lately.
Like, very distant, making up excuses not to be with me. I don't know.
Hey, do you think she's--
- No, forget it.
- What?
I don't know, dude. I've also noticed she's acting very weird.
You guys are always fighting. Maybe she's seeing someone else.
I've thought about it. She spends all her time with Juliana, and maybe she introduced someone to her.
Then you have to find out. I don't know, follow them, make sure she's not actually seeing anyone else.
Maybe she is and you'll be the last one to find out she's cheating on you.
She better not even think about it, because she'll regret it.
Miss Valentina, I'll wait for you in the car.
Hello.
Mom.
I brought you kiwis.
What is it? Something wrong?
What happened? Did the narcs come back?
No, it's not that, honey.
I haven't been feeling well lately.
I better get some rest.
I know her, Val, something's wrong.
Maybe not.
Maybe she's just not feeling well. We just left the hospital.
It's normal. She doesn't know the house, it's normal. Hey--
Hey.
Relax.
You two are safe, okay?