Well I-- I--
You're in love with a girl?
I mean, I think so.
I mean, I'm pretty sure I am.
But why are you crying?
There is--
Absolutely nothing wrong with it.
I thought you were going to tell me something... Actually serious.
I don't know what people are going to say when they hear that--
Dad! I mean, if he was alive, what would dad say?
Or mom. Or Eva! Can you imagine how Eva will be like?
No, no, no. But listen... Listen to me, Val.
It should not matter to you what people are going to say, understood?
What matters here is you.
Your feelings.
- I mean, do you still feel something for Lucho?
- No!
There's your answer!
You don't have to keep wondering.
But yes,
I do have to tell you that--
You need to tell him.
I don't think it's nice to cheat on anyone.
It's not pretty.
But I don't know what to tell him. What should I tell him?
Tell him whatever you're comfortable with.
But you have to be honest with him.
It's the least you can do.
And, well, who are we talking about?
Juliana?
What can I tell you?
I like it.
Because... I see you happy.
That's what matters the most to me.
Not having to put up with your bad mood.
Thank you.
Hey.
Where were you? I've been calling you.
What's wrong?
We need to... Talk. Please, come.