Oh, well, against all odds,
- We did it. And I think you have everything you need to survive in this house.
- I know.
- Cheers.
- Seriously, yeah. How lucky. We're lucky you rescued us.
Imagine if I'd left to another city.
Or country.
- Or whatever.
- Oh, no!
- No, don't say that.
- No.
- I'd die.
What's this?
"Death is Only a Portal"?
Yes, don't judge me, okay?
What is this?!
It's a book! An amazing book by Camilo Guerra.
Who is Camilo Guerra?
He's a friend of my dad's.
Sorry.
Very dear and very handsome, as you can see.
He's handsome.
And this book became like, a bible, because it's helped me a lot.
With dealing with my father's death, so.
How did it help you?
It made me consider that maybe he's not totally dead. Don't judge me!
- What?!
- Yes.
- That's what this book is about?
- No!
The book is about...
Reincarnation.
About reincarnation. And more specifically about
When you have unfinished business, you come back to life
To finish them. Don't you laugh!
- Why are you laughing? You don't believe me!
- Well, because these things are obviously not true.
- Of course they are.
- Of course not. Okay, listen.
Chino died. Strangely, he resurrected and on top of that
- He came back saying he was coming from a different life.
- Really? And you don't believe him?
- No!
- And you think I'm a fool too?
Come on, Val. Chino's head was obviously screwed up because of all the things he did.
Because of the way his brain got fried.
Or he was telling the truth!
No, Val! Look, obviously everything has a scientific explanation.
This book-- The same way you see Camilo here, so handsome!
He's also a scientist.
And the researches he does are totally serious, I'm telling you.
Oh, right.
I mean,
I know what we're going to do.
We're going to meet with him so he can explain his theories, because you're looking at me like I'm crazy.
- And, truly, when it comes out of his mouth, it makes a lot of sense.
- Okay, yeah.
Yeah? Okay.
Fine. It would be cool to see what he's going to tell me, the scientist.
Let's see what he says.