[SERGIO: Wanna meet up today?]
Mom?
We're having breakfast.
- Hello.
- Mom isn't here.
What? She disappeared?
I'm telling you, she's not here. I just woke up, looked for her and she's not here.
I need you to come, please, Panchito.
- Relax. I'm coming over.
- You're not going anywhere.
Can't those woman manage things on their own?
- Listen, Pancho, I'm telling you, if you put a foot out of this house--
- I'm sorry. I'll explain it to you latter. This is urgent.
- Little sister!
- Hello.
How you doing?
- What's the matter with you?
- What?
I know exactly why you're like this. I heard you coming home last night.
- Uh-huh.
- Don't act dumb.
- What?
How embarrassing. Look at your face, you're all--
In love. What's up? I mean, that face, those sparkling eyes.
And, oh, that brushed hair.
You know what? I should go to Valle more often, that's the truth.
It is the perfect place for secret love.
And you're telling me all the details right now.
I think I'm in love.
- Yeah, I've figured that.
- No, no, but--
This girl is incredible. She's humble, she's...
Fun, we laugh together.
She makes me a better person, you see?
- Oh, well, that is something. That's a hard thing.
- Why do you say that? Huh?
- What's the matter with you?
- Okay, okay. Fine.
Spill the beans. What I need to know is the name and last name. I want to know--
- Why do you--
- I need to know! Who is the woman that has you like this
Drooling. I want to know who it is you like so much--
Yes, Guille, come on, tell us. Who's this amazing woman that makes you so excited.
Huh?