We were better then ever.
We haven't argued in a while. Why do you want to break up?
Look, I know you've been trying really hard, okay?
And, really, I appreciate it. It makes all the difference, but it's just--
Right now, I'm--
I'm very confused.
Confused?
You're breaking up with me because you're confused? With what?!
It's been--
A very hard time. And I'm still--
A mess because of my father's death.
- I don't mean to hurt you, okay?
- Look, Val.
I understand perfectly how hard it is.
But it's a matter of time and I'm decided to accept.
And to wait for as long as you need.
You are not understanding.
Lucho, I don't want you to wait for me, okay?
It's over.
There's someone else, isn't there?
- No, there's no one else--
- You're not leaving until you tell me what's going on.
Who's the asshole you're with?
We're not finished talking. Who you're cheating on me with?
- No one!
- Who you're cheating on me with?
- Respect what I just told you!
- I won't let you go until you tell me who it is!
Hey, hey. What are you doing? Let her go. Let her go.
If you're caught making another scene, they're going to expel you.
Calm down, dude. Come on! Relax.
Hey, hey, hey. Relax, man.
I broke up with Lucho.
- What? You broke up with him?
- Yeah. I don't know how I did it, but it's done.
- But... Did you tell him everything that's happened?
- No, you're crazy? He'd kill me.
Juls.
I need to see you.
Can I come over?
Yes, obviously, come over. Yes, of course.
Okay, I'll see you there. Bye.