Won't you tell us who makes you so happy?
Look at you.
I-- I don't think you know her.
And...?
It's just an affair?
- No.
- Of course. Okay, it's fine.
Guille, it's fine that you have them. Okay?
Just be very careful. Don't get the girl pregnant
And have kids all around, because then what would you do with your life?
- Enjoy it. Enjoy it.
- Sorry, I have to take this.
We haven't finished this talk, ok?
So, my sister is kind of heavy during breakfast, huh?
Okay, let's see.
You may have gotten rid of her, but you will tell me.
- Who is she?
- Guess it.
Okay, okay, okay. Um...
Right. Paula?
- No.
- Is it Regina? She's that-- That blondie with--
- Okay. Um... It's Clau. The one that carries the envelopes?
- You know who! She's always bringing stuff to the--
- No.
Okay, well. Give me tips. You're obviously not helping me enough.
She works with me.
- Renata.
- Uh-huh.
- It's Renata? Oh! It's Renata!
- Quiet! She's going to hear you.
That pleases me, because, to be honest, I didn't trust your taste, but knowing it's...
Renata.
I feel-- I mean, it gets me in another mood, you know?
Like, she's cute, she's sweet, she's nice.
- What about you?
- I like her. What? Me?
Tell me your secret.
From the other day.
No, this-- This is not the right place, because
Eva's out there.
So... When it's my secret, it is a good place, right?
- But not yours?
- Well, it was your mistake, you're dumb.
You know what? Somewhere else. I'll tell you.
Let's go somewhere.
- Eat now.
- All right.