Paquito. Do you remember Paquito Galán?
He studied with us.
How can I not, we were all crazy about him.
Well, that 'all crazy for him'..
Last year, he got married, to whom? His boyfriend.
Paquito Galán with his boyfriend.
He married a man?
Yes.
He was the most handsome one in the class.
Come on.
He was the most intelligent one.
The only one to finish university. The only one.
I don't believe it.
He was a good person, very decent..
What had that got to do with anything, Lupita?
Being gay has nothing to do with whether you're a good or bad person.
You know in this country, equal marriage had been legalized for 8 years.
8 years.
Are you serious?
Yes. I'm serious.
And the world didn't end, the sky didn't fall down, nothing.
Everything is the same.
The same Lupita.
Maybe, you're right.
Panchito, I find it very hard to understand that my daughter...
Likes women.
These things are difficult to comprehend.
But for her, I am going to  try.
I'll try.