I have no words to thank you enough about what you've done for us.
It's nothing, I love you both a lot.
You know that you can count on me.
It's a very difficult situation.
I'm not here to argue.
I don't want to argue, I just want you to come back to the house...
You had a room, here you are sleeping in a cot.
I'm not coming back.
- Leave the tantrum.
- No, it's not a tantrum.
You know what have I been thinking?
That is time I do what I have to do with my life alone, and you start thinking what to do with yours too.
Do you hear yourself?
You are being impulsive again.
Just like what happened with Valentina.
So, you keep thinking that... that was an impulse.
- Valentina?
- Of course.
- No, it was not an impulse.
You didn't even give yourself a chance to have a boyfriend.
You don't know what it is to be with a man, a normal relationship.
Woman-Men. Normal.
Or what?
Since you were little you like girls?
I don't know.
I don't know mom, I don't know if I'm gay.
Well then, why did you tangle yourself with Valentina?
Mom, can you stop saying that I tangled myself with Valentina.
This is not a tangled thing, don't you understand? I didn't get tangled, I fell in love.