Hey.
What's up?
What's up, why are you here?
Well, I went to your house and your mom said you'd be here.
That's why I came.
Don't think I'm stalking you.
No. I didn't say that.
Okay.
Well, I came because I have news about Costa Rica.
Oh really?
Yes, I talked to someone who said he could give you work..
And also a place where to live.
Cool.
It's all solved.
That's so cool.
Yeah?
Let's go eat and I'll tell you how it's there and so on.
I can't, I'm working right now but...
Yes, go. Go eat with your friend.
You can relax and you can work tomorrow. Yes?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Take advantage it because I don't have classes today and I'm not free all the time.
Okay then. I'll go get my things and I'll come.
Go, go. Okay.
Thank you, Perlita.
Thank you.
If something happens to her...
Yes, yes, yes. I'll take care of her, don't worry.
Like the girl of your eyes.