Barreto is preparing a defense to prove that my brother had no idea of what was going to happen at the liquor store.
They want to prove that Toño lead him into it.
Toño has always been the type of guy who gets into trouble
And it was obvious that sooner or later he would get caught.
I just want Guille to be out of there as soon as possible. You know, because I-
I couldn't even sleep last night thinking about how he spent the night.
Calm down, he'll be fine.
It's okay.
My family is falling apart, Lucho.
I was thinking about that earlier.
I heard on the radio that...
Last night, your dad's body was stolen. Is that true?
I don't understand what's happening anymore.
Calm down.
Everything will be okay.
Juliana.
Juliana, wait.
Hey!