I was calling you.
Please.
Let me explain...
What happened.
Call me when you can.
My child.
Alirio is ready to take you to the police station.
Okay.
Could you tell him to wait for me a second?
Yes.
Thank you.
My child.
I just want you to understand that...
I wasn't taught...
I come from a world,
Where homosexuality is not natural.
And what is natural then?
Well, that..
A man and a woman having a family.
And that's what you'd be giving up if you're with Valentina.
So, do you think I'm thinking about having a family?
Do you think I want to have a family after the family that I've had?
I'm just getting to know what love is..
And I'm having a really bad time.
You know what, leave.
Really, leave.