She's still not answering my calls.
What if something happened to her?
Nothing happened.
Juliana is mad at you, that's why she's not answering, that's all.
But I'm so worried about where she slept.
Will you help me look for her?
Lupita.
Juliana is very smart.
She's gone through difficult things and she knows how to take care of herself.
Calm down.
Yes, you're right.
I'm not even hungry.
Juliana?
Mrs Perla, how are you?
Ah, what a relief.
I was desperate.
Thank you so much for taking care of my daughter.
Thank you for calling.
Yes, please.
She was with Mrs Perla?
Are you coming with me to the restaurant?
Look, Juliana is in a safe place.
It's better to give her time to think about things.
Yes, that's true.
And you..
You should think about how you're going to deal with her relationship with Valentina.
Because none of this is going to change.