Poor Guille, I can't believe this is happening.
What?
How can you say "poor Guille"? You have to be honest, he was looking for this.
Are you serious? That's the best you've got to say right now, Eva?
These are the moments where I miss dad the most.
Are you complaining about me?
No.
I'm doing everything I can.
I'm saying that I miss him and that he would know what to do.
Not everything has to do with you, okay?
Why are you speaking to me in that tone?
I don't know, because I'm tired and because, I don't know, we're not all like you.
What are you claiming, Vale? I was the first one who rushed to help Guille.
You rushed to help Guille for the family reputation, not because you care about my brother.
How can you say something like that, Valentina?
It's true.
That's why I can say it.
It's not...
Okay, enough. Stop arguing.
Eva, sit down.
Relax a little.
Guille's girlfriend explained to us what happened, so we're going to let the police and the lawyers do their jobs.
We don't benefit from looking for someone to blame.
The best thing we can do right now is to get some sleep.
Besides, Baretto is a very good lawyer.
Your dad always said so.
I'm sorry, Eva.
I'm sorry.