Come in.
You can stay here, in peace, until you leave for Costa Rica.
This is huge.
I don't know if I'll be able to pay you.
Hey, no one is asking you to.
It's important to give,
As it is to learn to receive. Okay?
That's what friends do.
And to celebrate that you have a new home,
I brought you this magic.
This mezcal is amazing. Lucho's family makes it.
Lucho is your best friend?
That dude...
He's a karma.
He's like a dog you love, but he keeps pissing on your rug and
Then you don't want him.
Look...
Lucho is a good guy.
What happens is that
He throws tantrums and things at home are rough, that's why he's like that.
If you'd known him before dating Valentina...
He was worse.
He's gotten better.
I ran into him at Valentina's house.
Really?
I thought they weren't talking anymore.
They were hugging.
Really?
Do you think they might make up?
I wouldn't know what to tell you.
With those two, I don't know what to expect.
They break up and make up, break up and make up.
They've been like that forever.
She manipulates him, he manipulates her.
They have a weird game going on.
Don't be surprise if one day you hear that they're back together again.