What am I going to do to get my daughter back?
Understand her.
How am I going to do that if I can't even talk to her?
I went to the restaurant, she told me to leave.
She's angry.
Give her time.
Well, maybe you're right.
It's just that... I find it hard to understand that my daughter likes another woman.
I don't know. Everything that happens to me is bad, it's like I'm cursed, it's all negative.
Wait, wait. What happened to Juliana is not bad.
I'm serious.
Oh please, don't start again.
You're always saying the same thing.
No, listen to me, listen to me.
To understand your daughter, the first thing you have to do is open your mind.
Understand that homosexuality is something common.
Everyone has a relative or friend who is homosexual.
Oh yeah, you're so open minded.
Like who?
Like who? I don't know anyone.