I didn't know you had this hacker side to you.
See, I'm not that stupid. I also have a geek side.
Lupita has been in the same place for a while, it doesn't make sense.
Well, here on the map, it looks like it’s in a residential zone and...
Maybe she got there and is waiting for an opportunity to enter? I don't know.
I think it’s best if you send that to Montilla, right?
I'm going to save these to your photos so you can send them by WhatsApp.
Okay.
Tell me.
Montilla, I'm Valentina Carvajal.
I just sent the location of where I think my friend Juliana is, to your phone.
Are you talking about the girl that was kidnapped?
Yes
Juliana.
How do you have the location?
Because.. Because...
We tracked down her mom who was kidnapped in the same place and she said she was going to rescue her.
Mrs Lupita went to Alacrán's house?
That's what I'm trying to say. Please do something.
I'm on my way.