You have a call.
He says it's El Chino.
What do you want?
Yes, hello?
Put it on speaker.
Hello.
What's going on, bro?
It's been a long time since I've known about you, right?
Since the cartel days.
Would you look at that..
I finally hear your voice, Chino.
Now all I need is to see your face.
I'm going to make that wish come true.
Do as I say.
So, do what I say, okay!
Don't fuck with me.
I have your daughter here.
Don't you dare touch her.
And if you want to see my face again...
You're going to do what I say.
[Motherfucker!]
Shameless!
Did you hear what I said or not?
Do you think Montilla has arrived at the narcos' house?
I'm sure he has, yes.
So why aren't they telling us anything?
Maybe we shouldn't have told the police and I was wrong.
Do you want to go?
There?
Yes.
It's so dangerous.
We can get closer and see what's happening. I'm sure the police have already entered and...
Maybe when we get there, they already have gotten Juliana out of there.
We could go stay at a..
Safe distance so we don't make anything worse, but so we're there.
Yes.
Right?
For Juliana.
Thank you.
You're welcome.