You were wrong to betray me, Chino!
Thanks to me, you made a lot of money.
What happened?
I got tired and didn't want to keep doing this. I didn't want to be killed, as you all will be.
The statistics say so.
Statistics?
This guy has been seen a lot of movies.
What was your plan, Chino?
Escape with the money and set up a...
A small store.
Why are you laughing?
It went wrong, huh?
Not that bad, right?
No?
You ended up in the electric chair.
I ended up in the electric chair, but here I am, alive and kicking.
And with the money and with the USB.
Let her go now!
I don't want to keep listening to you.
Well, I have the money and the USB so let go of my daughter now!
I don't trust you.
We're doing things my way.
Give me the USB.
Or I'll kill her first.
Then I'll kill you.
Let my daughter go.