Yes, okay.
Bye.
What's up? What happened?
I'm so..
I'm so scared.
Here, sit down.
Tell me, what happened?
Juliana was kidnapped.
Jacobo's daughter?
Jacobo, Chino, I don't even know what his name is anymore.
Do you know who took her?
The same people who took her mom, but
We really have to do something, Lucía because
No one is doing anything, okay?
Let's publish the news.
Yes.
Yes?
Yes, we'll do whatever it takes.
Please, because..
Yes, yes.
Count on it. Calm down.
The police aren't doing anything.
No, the police will...
No, they never do anything.
They will do their job and we will do what we can at the newspaper.
Don't think you've won yet because if Chino pulls one of his tricks..
I'm going to eat a taco of his grilled daughter.
And I know where I'm going to start.