Wait here a second, please.
Should I wait here for you, miss?
Yes, thank you.
Hi.
What's up? What are you doing here?
I was waiting to invite you to go eat.
It's a bad time, Lucho, honestly.
Please, let me invite you.
Hello.
Lupita has gone to Alacrán's house.
What?
Well, she was desperate and she said she was going to rescue Juliana herself.
Are you serious? And you let her go, just like that?
No, I didn't let her, she left. I went into the house to look for something and when I came back she was gone.
What are we going to do?
I don't know what to do.
Once those guys realize she's alive, they're going to kill her.
Do you know where Alacrán's house is, or not?
I have no idea.
You know what,
Even if Lupita gets mad,
I'm going to the police.
I already spoke to Montilla and told him Juliana was kidnapped.
Thank you.
Good.
Well, obviously, he doesn't have that information. Call him, please, and tell him that Lupita has gone to Alacrán's house.
Honestly...
Okay.
I'll do that now.
What happened?
I swear...
What happened? What happened?