What if Valentina is right and one man isn't enough to rescue Juliana?
I have to go to Alacrán's house.
No, no, no, you're not going anywhere.
Those guys have to keep thinking you're dead, Lupita.
I'm going to rescue Juliana.
You don't know what those guys are capable of.
If you go, you're going to complicate everything
And they are going to kill you.
I don't care.
I'm going to save my daughter.
No, no, no. Okay, okay.
Let's plan something together..
But something sensible.
Please.
Let me get you something to drink.
But you have to stay calm, okay?
Lupita...
Damn it.
Do you realize that being here is like putting a rope around our own necks?
Hey?
Beltrán.
I'm talking to you, Beltrán
Lower your voice.
I'm concentrating.
Concentrating on what? How they're going to kill us?
Alacrán is a man of his word.
As soon as I give him El Chino Valdés..
He will give me my daughter.
That's your plan? To turn me in?
The plan is to rescue Juliana.
I'm sorry, brother.
You would do exactly the same for your daughter.
So..
Give me your phone.
Go on, I have a nervous finger.
Move.