Montilla.
Juliana was kidnapped, I need you to help me find her, please.
Look, calm down. Sit down, lets...
No, I can't calm down because I know that the..
First hours in a kidnapping are crucial to find the victim. So we need to do something now!
Look, if you relax, sit down and let me explain, then I can do something.
If you don't, then I can't.
Okay.
She was taken from the..
Restaurant and I think that it was..
I think, it's the same people who are trying to find El Chino.
El Alacrán will be one step ahead of us.
What do you mean Alacrán is one step ahead of us?
She can't be kidnapped, okay? She has to be back here with me.
You have to prevent them from hurting her, please. What are we going to do?
Calm down. We're going to do what's best.
That is not what's best!
You need to do absolutely everything that's necessary to bring her back.
If you tell me that you will find her and she will be fine, then I will calm down.
Please.
We are going to do what's best, but I can't promise you anything.
What's happening?
Jacobo is back.
Is he with you?
He's waiting for you.
Do not let him leave.
I'm on my way.