El Chino is coming for you.
Chino will never come for me.
I'd take advantage and say goodbye.
I don't want to see Chino.
Perfect.
Today, he's going to die.
Go.
Go, go, go.
I am.
So, is she still there?
She's still there. She's still there.
Take this left.
Hurry, hurry. Please.
We're going. Valentina. Calm down, I'm going.
I'm doing what I can.
Go, go, go.
Go out. Let's go.
I'm going, wait.
Remember, lower your head. Lower your head.
Less. You're not begging for forgiveness.
Okay, okay.
That's it. Stare. When you see him..
Look tough.
Drop your shoulders. And forward, that's it.
You're going to say things that you've never said.
You're going to let go. Let out the animal you have inside.
That's it. Be confident.
Huh?
Like that.
I really don't like this place, Beltrán.
Walk, walk, walk, walk, walk.
What do you mean keep walking. Do you not care about your body getting shot?
I don't care, it's important that you walk.
This is not safe, Beltrán.
You're right, it's not safe.
Walk! If you stop, you'll be a dead man, damn it.
I'm covering you.