Well...
It's that...
I'm not your angel, I'm...
I'm your husband.
What are you saying?
I'm Chino Valdés.
What?
No. I don't understand anymore.
Every man that comes to this house is your husband?
I am the only husband she has, you imbecile.
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down.
What?
Are you going to complicate everything or what?
Tell my mom why you think you are El Chino.
Things from out of this world happened that...
I still can't understand.
When I was electrocuted, suddenly..
I appeared in this body and..
That's all, I have nothing more to explain to you, that's it.
I already told you.
I recognized you.
I saw it in your eyes.
And you denied it. You lied to me. You lied to me.
Mom, no, no. Calm down.
Mom, listen.
Stop.
No, 'stop', nothing!
Relax, Lupe. I'm here to tell you, okay?
Dead or alive, Chino has done nothing but ruin our lives.
Hey, Lupe.
Please.
'Please' nothing!
What happened to Chino was not God's will.
It wasn't mine either.
It was a curse and he deserved it.
I don't want to know anything about you.
Not as El Chino.
Not as an angel.