What is it?
The magic of the microwave.
Don't judge me. I may not be a cook but I'm a great witch.
Now, keep telling me about your daughter and Beltrán's daughter.
Are they girlfriends, how do they...
I don't have the details, there's a relationship.
That's it.
I can imagine Beltrán's face when he finds out.
He's so macho.
Are you finding this funny or?
Truthfully, yes.
But I don't think that it's a coincidence, it's destiny.
You were marked to find each other.
By the transmigration of your souls
Or by your daughters meeting.
Yes.
So one thing...
Perhaps...
Lead to the other.
I mean..
Yes, it's clear that this has some reason. I imagine this isn't just about me helping Beltrán
To save his daughter. There's got to be something more.
Yes.
Yes, what?
Do you need salt for...
It's good.