Lupita.
What is she doing here?
Why did you let her in?
If it wasn't for her, my daughter wouldn't have been kidnapped.
Calm down, please.
Valentina is worried, too.
Oh of course she's worried.
Yes.
It's all her fault, I don't want her here.
I don't want her here!
I'm sorry, Mrs, but if anyone is to blame, it's me.
Juliana was with me yesterday and I let her leave alone.
Who are you?
I'm a friend of...
He's your daughter's boyfriend.
But you don't have a problem with that, right?
Don't mock me.
I'm not joking, I'm serious.
Can we talk about what's important, please?
Valentina has a point, Lupita.
What do we know about Juliana?
The only thing I know is that my daughter is in danger.
Why do you think I'm here?