We've already passed this street, Lupita.
I'm not sure, all these houses look the same.
Yes, but we've been doing this for so long.
I'm going to ask some guys I know to take me to the area.
Wait, wait, wait.
Do I stop?
Here.
By those men.
That's the house.
My child.
Someone's looking for you.
Come in, please.
Thank you.
I can't believe it. You really had the guts to come here.
Can you just listen to me, please.
No, not really, no.
I don't want to.
You were like a brother to me and...
I can't believe you could do that to me. You don't do things like that.
We've been friends since we were kids.
I think you better leave.
I get that you're...
Sergio, I'm serious.
I understand perfectly why you're mad at me, okay?
I'm an idiot, I'm sorry.
Yes, you are an idiot.
But I came here because I have something important to tell you.
Juliana was kidnapped.
What?