Hey.
No.
I have to explain to you what happened.
I don't want to talk to you.
Juliana and I only..
Look, I'm going to say one thing.
The important thing right now is that she comes back safe and sound,
And I have no intention of knowing what happened between you two.
So leave it.
I'm running out of patience, girl.
Tell me where your dad is.
Or are we passed the screaming and begging?
Well, you're gonna have to kill me because I don't know where Chino is.
You've helped us a lot with Alacrán's location.
I will do the rest of the rescuing.
Whatever you want to do,
Just don't put my daughter's life at risk.
I won't.
Yours either.
I know how to handle these..
Rescue things, very well.
Relax.
You really think that Jacobo..
is El Chino?
He looks just like him.
The eyes..
The face is the same.
Well, yes..
But
If you look closely...
Let's not waste time discussing this.
Your daughter is in danger, so..
We will talk later.
Go inside.