I told you, he left.
He didn't care about your threats.
Why do these things keep happening to me?
Don't you dare tell me absolutely nothing, Beltrán, because I'm fed up.
Fed up of everything.
This is about my daughter's life.
Don't you get that we're running out of time?
Here.
Take it.
See, I'm not that bad.
What happens is that, in this business..
Betrayal is paid for with life.
And El Chino has been escaping responsibility for a long time.
And you know who's next on the list?
The family.
But, hey.
I've like you since the first time I saw you.
Maybe we can pay this debt in another way.
I also love fresh meat.
What do you say?
I'd rather burn to death than be with someone as disgusting as you.
If only you knew the success I have with high society women.
They even call me to make babies.
That's suicide.
Well, it's over.
Turn on the grill.
Also, cover your ears, this one is going to scream worse than a pig.
Alacrán.
We just got a message from Chino.
El Chino? Hold on.
Let me see.
See.
It's seems like your dad still loves you.
He says he is going to give himself up for you.