No, no, please, no.
No, I told you I don't know anything, I swear.
Okay, little girl.
No.
I'll give you one last opportunity.
You either tell us, or I'll feed you to the dogs.
I've told you, I don't know anything. I swear, please..
Don't hurt me, I have nothing to do with this.
What a shame such a pretty face like yours
Has to be wasted, for a guy who is worthless.
I swear, the last time I seen him was at the hospital, when he killed Servando Armenta.
And then all I know is that he ran away because he knew he would get killed, please.
Look no more.
Chino, always being careful.
He says that his name isn't Chino, that it's Jacobo.
And now he's lost his memory, too.
Please, please. Don't hurt me, I swear I don't know anything. I swear.