You don't get how hard it was for me to understand all of this.
The man with Chino's face and Chino's body is not Chino.
And now it turns out that Beltrán has him and is going to exchange him for my daughter.
This is all very complicated.
What worries me is that...
If he is telling the truth and has nothing to do with this and gets killed...
Lupita.
If this man has the face of Chino Valdés, he is Chino Valdés.
It's him.
It's Beltrán.
I have to go.
I'll go with you.
No, you're not coming. I can't put you in danger.
I'll go with you to look out for you.
No, no Pancho.
I'm going to see Jacobo, I need to clear this up.
I don't know if it's a good idea to give him to Alacrán.
Okay.
Be careful.
Are you listening?
Hey.
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
So leave that then.
I'm asking you that if you know Beltrán better than me,
Would he really be capable of turning me in, or not?
The truth is that..
I've never seen him like this. So...
So desperate.
Well, that's normal, no?
I have a daughter. I think any man would do that for his daughter.
But you also have your life and..
Well..
I mean León Carvajal does.
I...this is a mess, honestly.
Yes, I know this is a mess, but it's bigger than Chino's and the transmigrated bodies.
What? Explain. You're like Beltrán, I don't understand what you're saying. What?
It's that his daughter and my daughter...
What?
Nothing, they're..
They're in love.