Why didn't you go to the police? I don't understand.
I've already told you.
Beltrán is in charge.
You're going to leave your daughter's life in the hands of someone we don't know?
Beltrán saved my life when those narcos were going to kill me.
He knows how to deal with them, he has a plan.
It doesn't matter that he has a plan. You're being so naive, really.
Can you calm down, please?
She's her mom, I'm sure she knows what she's doing, okay?
Calm down.
Are you really dating my daughter?
I can't believe that is a priority for you right now.
It really doesn't matter who your daughter is with. Whether she's with me or with him.
You know that your daughter is an important person in my life
And I'm not going to sit here with my arms crossed, okay?
I'm going to do something!
Val.
Val, wait.
You know, I think you should go home in a taxi because..
I don't want to be with you.
Hey, look.
What happened is serious, okay. You shouldn't be alone.
How nice.
How nice of you, now you want to be a friend and worry about me.
I don't want to forgive you, you crossed the line.
You shouldn't have done that.