Guille?
How you doing?
I imagined it was you. It's good that it is.
I'm glad to see you.
How have you been?
Um... Well, it's questionable, to be honest. It's questionable.
So much has happened since you left.
How are you?
I could be better.
My tires were stolen.
- I can't buy new ones because I don't have a penny.
- Poor thing.
And I can't find a job.
- I'll buy you new tires, if you want.
- Nah, it's fine.
But it has been a little harder that I thought it would be.
But that's life.
And you? How are you?
It has also been a little harder than I thought it would be.
I didn't think the reaction at the university would be like this, to be honest.
They have all taken Lucho's side, so...
Well, maybe things like these are supposed to happen.
So we can finally live the lives we want to.
It takes a little suffering, right?
More?
You know?
The truth is everything is easier when we're together.
- Please, don't be away.
- I won't be away.
I promise.
Plus, I want you to meet Renata.
Let's run away, the four of us, please?