My girl?
You have a visitor.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here? I swear, if you're here because of Lucho--
Lucho didn't send me, I came here on my own.
To be honest, I didn't like the way they treated you at the University, so
That's why I'm here.
I have no problem with you and Juliana dating.
On the contrary.
It's cool, I support you.
Really?
Yes, really.
Swear it.
And, well...
I also came because
It was my fault that everyone found out you changed Lucho for Juliana.
How? I mean, Why--? Why would you do something like that?
I was an idiot! Really, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Don't be mad at me. I was really drunk and
It just came out. I told Nayeli and--
- Oh, Nayeli. Perfect.
- Damn Nayeli told everyone and all of that happened.
Honestly, I'm sorry.
I suppose everyone would find out anyway.
Hey.
I'm on your side.
Whatever you guys need, seriously,
You can ask me.
And don't even worry about the people at the University.
They'll get over it and go back to normal and if not,
I'll take care of those idiots.
And, well.
I also wanted to congratulate you for having such good taste, 'cause
What an upgrade, huh? Going from Lucho to Juliana?
Wow!