If I’m being honest, I didn't think you would come.
Not to offend you but honestly...
I needed to get out of the house.
I'm not offended, don't worry, I understand.
Hey, do people at your house know about you and Val?
They won't know.
Because?
Because Val and I broke up.
No way.
Really?
Really, it was for the best.
Her family would never get it, besides..
Look at everything that happened at the university.
Yeah..
Things got messed up but hey, people forget these things quickly so...
It will all pass with time and space.
I don't think that will happen with Eva Carvajal.
Yes, Val's sister is very intense.
But, you guys are old enough, you can do what you want.
It's much more complicated than that, Sergio.