Explain to me what your are thinking showing up at Juliana's house to insult her?
Valentina.
In her own house? I don't understand.
Vale, please don't shout we are working, okay?
Are you embarrassed? Well, I am embarrassed that you showed up at her home to insult her.
You are crazy, you really are!
Vale,
Valentina, you can't say this to me while I'm working, you have to leave us alone.
I'm going to explain because evidently this is all very confusing.
What happened is that my sister doesn't like the fact that I like women.
Valentina, enough, shut up.
Enough Valentina. Stop!
Mr. Ortis, could you leave us alone?
Vale, what is wrong with you?
It's not even that I like women,
I like one woman.
An incredible woman, who makes me a better person and you're keeping her away from me.
Valentina, I don't care. Listen to me.
You can't come here and shout at my work.
You're confused, you don't know what you're saying, you don't know what you're feeling.
I am not confused!
Yes you are!
No, I'm not confused.
You are confused. You think you can look at me and tell me what I feel.
Okay, I have had enough of this topic. Enough.
You are not my dad, so leave me alone.
No, I am not your dad, so listen to me carefully,
The relationship you have with that girl is over!
Yeah, it really is over.
You know, now she doesn't want to see me and,
I don't blame her because nobody likes it when someone comes to their home to call them a thief.