- Good morning, Alirio, how are you?
- Good morning, how are you? I'm very good.
I need to talk to you.
Oh, of course, how can I help you?
Look, I heard that you have been taking Valentina to see her friend Juliana.
Yes, yes.
- I need to ask you a few questions, let's go.
- Of course, ma'am.
The first thing I need to know is...
- Where are you going, honey?
- To buy some medicines.
I'll be right back.
- Well, I'm going to take a bath.
- Okay.
- Don't take too long, okay?
- No.
It's fine.
- Oh!
- Hello.
Juliana, right?
Yes, how are you?
I'm impressed.
First you seduce Valentina,
Then you come to live here, in my Chivis' house.
What do you want to do next, huh?
To live in my father's house?
Look.
I know Val is very naive and she sometimes lives in her wonderland world,
But not me.
I'm her big sister and I will always be here to protect her from people like you.
Look Eva, I don't have bad intentions. I don't want to take advantage.
What I feel for Valentina is real.
Look, I have nothing against gays.
Seriously. I'm in favor of sexual diversity.
That they adopt kids, get married, have parades.
But all that away from my family.
So I'm going to ask you to stay away from my sister,
Before you ruin her life.
Or I will have to ruin yours.