- Hey.
- No, wait, wait. Come out here.
What?
What is it?
- What happened?
- Your sister just left.
- Eva?
- Yes.
Why? What-- I mean, what was Eva doing here here?
- What do you think?
- I don't know. I have no idea.
To tell me to stay away from you, Val.
Are you serious?
I can't believe this.
Honestly, what is happening? Why--
- Why is everyone against us? I don't get it.
- I don't know. Plus, you didn't see the way she talked to me.
- She didn't even greet me.
- But do something.
- Val!
- Honestly, I-- This makes me very anxious.
Hold on. Wait a second.
Hello.
Juliana, who knocked?
Valentina, mom, we're gonna hang out for a little while.
Okay.
- Val.
- What?
- We can't talk here.
- Then let's go somewhere else.
Val.
Val, wait for me?
Valentina!
I'm sorry, but Miss Juliana can't get into the car.
- Excuse me?
- What?
I have been given orders by Mrs. Eva.
None of the drivers can allow you to get into the family's cars.
- Are you serious?
- Or any of the properties.
- No way.
- Of course.
I mean... No.
Look, Alirio, I've had a very bad day so I'm asking you to, please, get out of the way.
- Please, Miss Valentina, please don't get me into trouble.
- Alirio, what are you doing? Move.
Hey, Valentina! Calm down!
Don't yell at him. It's not his fault, anyway.
Come on. Let's go.
Val.