[From princess to dyke.]
Are these people really your friends?
They were my friends.
I also can't believe your sister Eva knocked on my door to tell me to stay away from you.
And to call you an opportunist.
Uh-huh.
I really don't know what's happening.
I don't understand.
Val, I don't know if we should continue with this.
With what?
With us being together.
What about our pact?
We were naive, Val.
I'm willing to give up whatever I have to, I will fight anyone.
- I don't care if it's my family, my friends, I don't care. So I can be with you.
- No, Val. I'm not.
- Oh, no?
- No.
- No?
- No!
I mean, no. My mom just got out of the hospital.
- The narcs are looking for her.
- What does that have to do with anything?
- I don't even know how long I will be in this city.
- It doesn't matter!
- It does matter, Val!
- Why are you saying this now?
- I don't understand why you're saying this.
- Val, I don't know how my mom will react.
- It doesn't matter how your mom will react, Juliana!
- Look, Val!
Don't you realize how complicated this is getting?
- I do not care!
- And I don't want to affect your life even more.
My life is already affected, Juliana!
You know? Let's not--
Let's not look for each other anymore, okay?