So, now I need to get out of the city with my mum.
Why is that?
Because my mum is sick.
You're right, it is complicated.
And have you thought about where you would go?
I have no idea.
Well if it is any help to you, I spent some time in Costa Rica and it was really, really cool.
I was there for 2 months and when I arrived, they gave me food and work. So?
Really?
Yes.
But, it is Costa Rica, so I don't know if that is too far?
Okay, tell me more.
Okay, look..
I have photos from my trip.
Have a look.
Hey, would it be really hard to find a job there?
If you want, I can put you in contact with who hired me and I don't think it would be a problem.
We can give it a shot, right.
Yeah?
When do you want to leave?
I want to go as soon as possible.