You know what? I'll drive, you're very drunk.
What would I do without you, champ?
You're my best friend, you know.
I thought that was Lucho.
That guy...
Well, are you gonna tell me why you fought, or not?
The truth is, Lucho's an idiot.
He thinks he's a man but he's just a little girl.
and when things don't go how he wants,
he has a tantrum.
But he is still your best friend.
No, not anymore.
I'm sick of him and his stupidity.
On one hand I understand Valentina, replacing him with someone else.
What a pain to deal with a dude like that.
And Juliana is pretty,
she's beautiful.
Wait, what? You're talking about Valentina's friend, The one you like?
Yes.
Her.
She and Valentina voted us out,
now they're together.
What?
You're telling me Valentina left Lucho for a woman?
Yeah.
I can't believe it.
No, I'm not saying anything.