What were those screams?
I was arguing with Valentina
Why?
Why? Because of that supposed relationship she has with that Juliana girl.
Okay, so what's the problem?
What is the problem?
My sister is not gay, she has always had boyfriends for god sake. She is confused.
Eva, being gay is something personal. Besides, who cares?
I care a lot because this family can't take another scandal.
Imagine what society would have to say.
Society can say whatever it wants. We are in the 21st century, you can't think like that.
Oh Mateo. As always, I'm the only one who cares about the reputation of this family.
Yeah, you worry now.. but you have told me what happened when you were in university and...
Mateo! That was a long time ago, it's not important.
I can't believe you would bring this up now that I am a married and respected woman. What is wrong with you?
So being gay can't be respected or what?
As always, you are never on my side, you never supported me.
But it's fine, don't worry. I'm going to get Valentina out of that absurd fantasy she is living in.
Look Eva, leave her in peace, it is her life.
She is my sister. And she doesn't know what she is doing.
And I'm asking you to do me a favour and do not interfere.
Nayeli.
If I had known, I wouldn't have slept at her house.
[Homophobic comments]
Lucho was kicked out of the trio.
Dyke princess.