What's going on, honey? You look even more crushed than last night.
Come on, Juli. Tell me.
You're not going to say anything?
We used to tell each other everything.
Mom, leave it.
I don't want to talk.
Okay, but I just want to know what's going on.
You have a boyfriend and you had a fight with him?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Did you fight with your friend?
Mhmm.
I knew it.
You had a fight with Valentina.
It was obvious it was going to happen.
That girl is... Beautiful, she's a good person, likeable, but--
She's from a different world, Juli.
- You two are like water and oil--
- And who asked for your opinion?
Fine, but don't be like that.
No, I will be like that.
I don't interfere in your thing with Panchito, do I?
- I don't say that you take advantage of him because he has feelings for you.
- That's not true!
It is true, because you only speak to him when you feel like it.
Don't be rude! Do not speak to me like that!
Well, don't stick you nose in my business and that's it! How about that?