Miss.
Is something wrong?
Everything, Jacobo.
Has the drunk man come to bother you again?
It's that people are very cruel. Very cruel.
Let's see, tell me what's wrong.
I feel alone.
I have no friends.
Guille left the house.
Why did Guille leave the house?
He fought with Eva. Maybe I should do the same.
Ahh don't say that.
Seriously, I'm being serious.
Your father broke his back all his life to give you...
this house with everything you have. And the reality is that you have an older sister and you can rely on her.
Older sister..
An older sister who is an authoritarian, aggressive...
who I don't care for, she doesn't help me at all.
Life is full of bad moments, now all we have left is to confront them.
I know, I have to be strong.
Strong, weak. It's fine to be vulnerable too.
Thank you.
I don't know how, but you always have perfect timing.