No, no, wait, no.
What do you mean he's my dad?
I've been trying to explain for a long time.
No, what are you saying?
I'll explain later, okay?
No, explain it now.
Let's go.
Go where?
I've already done what I came to do, the police can handle the rest.
What? No, I'm not going without my mom!
You'll do what I say to do.
The important thing is that we get out of here safely.
Do you recognize me now?
Let's go.
They don't listen.
Where is Juliana?
Where is she?
Ladies..
We have to go.
We want to see what is happening with Juliana's case and there's no point keeping us locked in here.
What is going on?
You have to wait for Inspector Montilla and he will let you know.
Please.
No.
I don't want to wait for anyone. I want to leave, please.
Miss, you can't leave.
I'm going to leave.
By the way, I have news for you.
I don't know if you have heard but...
Your brother was released today.
I didn't know if you knew?
Guille was released?
Yes.
He's out.
Guille was released.
It's Valentina.
Little sister..
I'm a free man.
What do you think?
That's great Guille, I've just found out.
I'm at the police station.
What are you doing there?
Lucho was killed.
Lucho?
Who?
It's complicated, it's only just happened.
I'll tell you later.
Okay, don't move. I'm on my way.
What's happening, Guille? Who's Lucho?
Come with me, I'll tell you.