This woman is still alive?
You're a dumbass.
How many lives do you all have?
Let her go.
I'll do anything you ask, but please let her go.
I don't care how many lives you have.
Today they're all going to end.
Kill her.
No, no.
No, we had a deal.
What?
Hey?
You're lucky that Alacrán will be the one to kill you.
Kill her.
No, no, no, mom!
Help!
Mrs, what's happening? Are you okay?
Help me.
Lupita! What about Juliana?
Calm down, please. They're women.
Calm down? I'm not calm.
Hello.
No, please.
Hey, please.
Please, don't do it.
Let's go!
Lucho, Lucho.
Lucho!
Surround the perimeter.
Enter the house.
What do we do? Someone help me, please!
Call an ambulance!
Please!
The USB.
I have the USB.
Run! Run!