No, no, no, no, no. They...
They grabbed me for killing a judge, remember? I was sent to the electric chair.
That was Chino, not you.
Okay, listen. Then you saw a guy come out of the morgue, right?
As if nothing had happened, as if he hadn't received 2,500 volts.
Did you see it or not?
Yes, obviously.
It's weird, no?
Yes, it's really weird.
Well, that guy you seen...
Is Jacobo, the man outside.
He's not your father.
Your father is here, in the body of a university teacher.
And don't give me that face.
It's weird.
Everyone does that.
It's the truth, what do you want me to do?
Of course they do. I know what is happening.
What?
Clearly, Chino is paying you, right? To say these things.
Why are you so stubborn?
Like always!
Listen!
Why would I go through all of this to rescue you?
That's the problem.
El Chino would never do that because El Chino doesn't care about me, okay?
Chino never wanted to recognize that he was my dad.
Are you going back there again?
Again...
Of course, he's leaving.
He's going to his other house that...
Other house? Shut your mouth, okay. There is no other house.
Until when, are you going to keep taking risks with your family?
Your daughter is figuring out...
My daughter?
Yes, your daughter.
Again you tell me about 'my daughter'.
Chino, please.
Chino, nothing.
Not again with 'my daughter'.
Is it really difficult to explain to me what you do?
I understand why you say that.
The truth is, I wasn't a good guy with you when you were a little girl, but...
There is a reason that you don't know.
Your mother cheated on me with a guy.
And I never
Believed that you were my daughter.