Well, I don't think it's that strange because
He is a hitman.
I can imagine.
What does that have to do with him being at the kidnapping of his own daughter?
I don't think so.
Maybe it's his fault that they took her?
It all happened so fast.
We...
We got there,
Lupita showed up and a guy came behind her and he
Didn't give him a chance to do or say anything and..
He shot him.
I'm sorry you're going through so much pain, Valentina.
It's unbelievable, I can't..
Believe for such a long time...
We had a criminal among us.
Hey, we're not sure about that, Johnny.
Guille, I know that it's..
It's a surprise for everyone but..
From what I know,
Jacobo is a good person.
We all thought the same but..
Even Interpol are looking for him and..
It could be a mistake.
It could be.
Valentina.
I'm here for whatever you need.
I'm so sorry.
It's nice to see you here, Guille.
And thank you, really.
I know you had something to do with my release.
I did what I had to do.
Thank you.
Let's go to the studio, I need to talk to you.
Hey.