Calm down.
It's all my fault.
Valentina, don't say that.
I shouldn't have left him.
It's not your fault.
I'll get her some water.
Okay, thank you.
Clearly, it's my fault.
Don't say that. Hey, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Don't you dare say that.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault and...
No, no.
Those people have to pay.
They're going to.
No, no, you're wrong.
The police..
The police will get them, Valentina.
I really don't understand.
I swear, they need to catch them.
They're going to.
They will catch who's guilty. Listen to me, Valentina. Look at me.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself because you're not to blame.
Calm down.
Please.. please..
Please.. Don't go..
Don't go, please because..
Renata and I are going to stay for as long as necessary. Until you're okay.
You're not going to be alone.
Okay?
I'm sorry, Vale.
You know, you always have my support.
I'll always be here for you.
What happened?
What happened is that, Valentina's friend, Juliana was kidnapped and..
There was a confrontation between the criminals and the police
And unfortunately, Lucho, her boyfriend...
Died.
What?
Valentina, I'm so sorry.
Valentina was there when it happened.
Jacobo, too.
Jacobo?