Mom, I'm okay.
Beltrán is with me, he will take me home later.
Juliana showed up.
She messaged me to say she's okay.
She's with Beltrán.
Are you serious?
Come here. That's good.
You shouldn't have gone to that place, girl.
You didn't think about what you could be exposed to.
You had already done enough giving us the address  and warning us of the kidnapping.
I want to see Lucho.
That's not possible at the moment.
You'll have to wait until the funeral.
Besides, we still need your statement.
What's wrong with you?
With everything that's happened, she shouldn't even be here.
Can't you see the state that this girl is in?
When she feels better, she will come back and give her statement.
Fine.
Call someone to come for you.
I didn't know it was you who called the police.
Thank you.