I'm scared to open the door.
You bring more people every time.
Who is this?
My daughter.
Enough with this, okay?
The one who has the face and body of my dad is him, not you.
You're driving me crazy, you're both wrong.
Hey, look, look...
But, this is...
It's the truth.
I just hope that the shot I fired puts Alacrán...
Out of business.
It’s best if the police get him, no?
No, if the police get him, it will be like nothing happened. He'd escape.
Do you want something to drink?
Yes?
Yes, thank you.
I don't understand why you had to tell the girl the truth.
Surely, she wasn't prepared.
That's not it.
It's not about whether she's prepared or not, it's about telling her the truth, right?
Yes, but..
Excuse me for saying this but, it's not your place to gossip.
Ah, gossip?
Yes, gossip.
So, you think I have nothing to do with her?
Well, you're right.
After what's happened, the least someone could do was tell her the truth, no?
And you?
Me, what?
When are you going to tell the truth to yours?
Surely, they're very confused too.