I want to report the kidnapping of my daughter.
My name is Lupita Valdés and...
What are you doing? I'm calling the police.
Don't get the police involved, they'll mess it up.
They don't know how to confront a narco.
And how do you know a narco took my daughter?
This is not a normal kidnapping.
It's Alacran's people.
But, I have friends who can help me rescue Juliana.
How do you have friends like that if you're a professor?
In this business, the less you ask the better.
Business?
But you're a stranger. I'm not going to put my daughter's life in your hands.
I'm going to the police.
Lupita, what are you doing?
Do you want to risk Juliana's life, or what?
I'm sorry.
Listen, I'm a man who keeps his word.
I won't fail you.
I swear on my life.
I am going to rescue Juliana.
Calm down.