Thank you, Lupita.
Do you know when you're leaving?
Not yet.
Why do you have that face?
Something happened?
Did that guy do something to you?
No, no.
No, Panchito has always behaved well with me.
The problem is my daughter.
Juliana.
What's happened with Juliana?
She left home.
What do you mean she left home? Where has she gone?
It's hard for me to tell you but...
Since you're a professor and...
You must be used to dealing with kids..
You can understand and even advise me, right?
Okay, I can give you advice. What happened?
I found out that my daughter is in a homosexual relationship.
Can you repeat that? I don't understand.
That my daughter...
Likes women.
What?