You know, since my dad died...
There isn't a single bit of good news in this house. Everything is..
Negative. I don't know what...
I don't know what's happening.
What?
I have good news.
I mean it.
Are you serious?
You're going to be an aunt.
You're going to be an aunt, Vale.
Stop.
I'm super sensitive right now, don't play with me.
I'm not joking.
No, no. It's the truth.
Eva is pregnant, you're gonna be an aunt.
I am?
Yes.
I'm going to be an aunt?
Yes, you'll be an aunt.
Really?
Yes, really.
I can't believe it.
I'm going to be an aunt!
You're going to be an aunt.
Can I be the godmother to?
Wait a minute..
It has to be named Valentina.
Please, it's a great name., you have to call it Valentina.
We have to talk to Eva.
Is everything okay?
I know.
I know. I can't believe I'm going to be the godmother. We talked and I'm going to be the godmother.
And it will be named Valentina, or Valentino.
Mateo.
I said we were going to wait to tell everyone.
I had to tell your sister, how can I not? She's going to be an aunt, my love.
Baby...
Come on, my love. Not that face, I had to tell your sister.
I'm so happy.