What are you talking about? Who is 'El Chino'?
My ex-husband.
Your ex-husband? As far as I know, you're still married.
He disappeared.
But we aren't talking about that.
Who are you?
Your guardian angel, didn't you say?
You reacted exactly the same as Juliana's father would.
Why do you talk to me like you've known me for years?
Anyone...
Would say the same thing about a girl who you are in charge of...
Growing up crooked.
Why do you blame me?
You don't know me.
Or do you?
Hello.
Lupita, something frightening happened.
Juliana was kidnapped.
What do you mean Juliana was kidnapped?
Yes, she is taken by some men.
It just happened. That's why I'm calling you.
I'm going to call the police right away.
What happened?
Juliana was kidnapped!
What?