You should have seen,
Guille felt very guilty from the beginning.
The whole time he was..
Miles away, unfocused, like very tense, very nervous, very stressed.
And he was looking for a way to help Mr Castillo but we didn't know how.
Okay, and what happened? What did you do?
We pretended to be a foundation.
A foundation?
Yes, and we offered our help.
That was they only way we could reach them where they would accept us.
Okay, so you were in contact with them. You saw them, you visited them.
Well yes, more or less.
We visited them.
Guille was always looking out for them.
He paid for Mr Castillo's operation, his wheelchair...
His physical therapy.
Plus, they even became friends.
Poor Guille.
Then we have to do something because if they were friends,
We have to explain to this person.
No, Valentina. I'd love to, I swear but..
Yesterday, when I left their house..
They were so hurt.
Renata, we have to try, we have to do something.
They were disappointed.
You don't know the look they gave me.
They felt betrayed.
I don't think they will forgive us.
Ren, we have to try.
I'm so scared, Valentina.
I'm so scared that they will take this case to it's last consequences.