Hey.
So, what's up?
What do you think?
I feel bad.
Well, that's normal after the half bottle of mezcal we drank.
But that's not what I want to know.
What I want to know is if you liked being with me?
I feel like I betrayed Valentina.
Look...
First of all, you and Valentina aren't together anymore.
Secondly, all of this as for exploration..
And to discover what's going on with you,
And all that.
So...
What's up?
Are you gay?
Bisexual?
Or what?
I want to go.
No, don't go, wait.
You don't have to leave, this is all paid for.
My plan was for you to have fun, for us to have a good time.
Not to make you uncomfortable.
Hey, hey. Wait.
It was here.
I saw them kissing.
It's your fault.
What?
What do you mean what?
Juliana is your responsibility and you couldn't even do that.
Why are you saying that?
How?
Why?!
Juliana is a girl.
You couldn't handle her and now what is she doing?
She's doing whatever she wants to.
Chino?