That's not even the worst. We were in the middle of the kiss..
And it began to sting more.
She started shouting and we had to get out because we couldn't take the itching.
And what was it?
A jellyfish.
Do you know how to stop the itching?
With piss.
I really can't believe that you don't like men.
I can't believe it.
Who told you I don't like men?
Okay, so..
You're bisexual?
I don't know.
I think you're confused.
Look, Valentina is very nice and..
That's what probably made you fall in love with her.
Sometimes, she's manipulative,
I've know her for a long time and I think that maybe that's why...
Okay.
Okay, very good.
What's up?
Did you like it?
I don't know.
I like it. I like this experiment.
Let's continue.
Take advantage. I'm not going to charge you.
I'm only offering because it's you.
And plus, we can clarify what you're feeling and see what's going on with you.
Okay, are you scared to see what happens?