You're shameless for coming here.
Calm down Ma'am. Please listen, we want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to anyone who has anything to do with that criminal.
Guillermo is not a criminal, okay?
Please, I'm asking you to take the time to watch the video again because
You will see that he is trying to stop the assault and he is just as surprised.
Exactly.
If it had been on purpose, he would not have helped you. You have seen everything he has done for you.
Who are you?
I'm his sister, okay. It's very frustrating to see my brother paying for something he didn't do.
Guille is from a good family.
They are not criminals.
I'm very sorry but it's that..
My brother-in-law is in a wheelchair now and..
Someone has to pay and...
Your brother is guilty, he was there with his friend.
I'm very sorry.
And in these pages you can find information on homosexuality.
There are so many things.
Everything, and plus...
You can make an appointment to see a specialist.
Oh, no.
Panchito, it's too much information.
Lupita, you have to do it so you can understand it better.
You think so? I don't know..
Yes.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Wait.
Yes, yes.
He's here again?
Don't you have a job? You are here all the time.
I need to speak to you Lupita, but..
Alone.