Perlita.
Juliana.
So good to see you, my girl.
How are you?
Do you need something?
Yes. Honestly, I do, Perlita.
I wanted to ask you for a favor.
I wanted to see if you could give me a job.
Let's see what I can get you.
Don't worry.
I care about you a lot and if I can help you out,
I'm happy to.
Thank you.
How is your mom?
Good, good. She's much better.
I'm going to get you some verdolagas for you to take home...
No, Perlita. No.
What?
I'm no longer living with her.
How?
Where are you living?
It's nothing, I was thinking about finding a hotel while I find somewhere...
No, no. You're not staying at a hotel.
No, I won't allow it.
Stay here, we have a cot.
At least until we find something better.
Yes.
Yes, that would really help.
Of course.
Thank you, Perlita.
Let's go.
I'll go get you some things.
Thank you.