The problem is the video.
Although, it could be the solution.
What do you mean by that?
Guille appears in the video with an accomplice.
Toño. But he doesn't want to talk about anything.
Toño who?
Antonio Peñaloza? His friend?
Exactly, that's him.
They've been friends his whole life.
You knew?
That Guille wasn't alone?
Well, that's what I've been trying to tell you.
Guille told me everything.
Okay, tell us what happened.
Okay.
It was all Toño's idea.
One day they were drinking some beers,
And Toño came up with the idea to live an adventure.
Something new for them.
Of course Guille didn't know they were going to rob a liquor store.
When they were there,
In the fear of everything, Guille couldn't get away.
And Toño fired a shot that hit the owner.
I don't believe this.
Such a silly way for Guille to ruin his own life.
Okay, Eva. I've already explained to Renata that it was an accident.
So what can we do?
Nothing.
Baratto, does this information help get Guille out?
Yes, of course, but we have to find this Toño.
And we need a copy of that video.
I really need my brother to get out of here today.
That's not possible because by law,
You have to stay in custody for at least 48 house.
No, no.
Yes.
Besides, at this time, it's too late to do anything.
I advise you to get some sleep.
Early tomorrow, I'll see what I can do.
Please.