Eva.
Ah Baretto, I'm glad you're here.
Things are very bad.
Is it true they're blaming Guille for the assault?
Yes.
Apparently, a man was injured, who fortunately for us, is still alive.
Baretto..
I need you to get my brother out of this place.
Well, first I need to talk to him.
I also have to see what the situation is with the police.
But I will ask that they let me see him, okay?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Renata.
Valentina.
What's wrong?
We were in Mrs Castillo's house when the police arrived and..
Renata.
You can't say anything.
Do you not realise that anything you say is going to be used against Guillemo.
Relax, Eva.
No, you too, Lucía, why did you bring Valentina?
She's in a bad place after everything that has happened, she's sensitive.
I'm right here, okay.
I'm listening and I also want to know what happened with Guille, okay?
Do whatever you want.
We will.
Can we help you with anything?
I'm so scared.
No, everything will be okay.
He'll be out soon.