Hey, I'm so proud of you.
It's not easy.
You did good.
It's cold.
Val.
What are you doing here?
Please tell me you didn't come to talk about the same thing again, please.
Valentina, you asked for it.
And I'm not referring to the narcos because...
That was really horrible and I'm so glad that you're okay.
But the rest..
What?
What do you me "what" Valentina,
I don't want to bother you, or talk about any of that.
But...
The reality is that, since we broke up your life has gone out of control.
You came to tell me that..
You're my axis, that kept me in line...
That's what I need to hear, yeah..
I didn't say that, Valentina.
But you have to realize that,
You're easily influenced.
I'm easily influenced?
Yes.
That's why Juliana got what she wanted.
And how do you know that it wasn't me who got what I wanted?