Not only that, but this could be a scandal that ruins my daughter's life.
Don't fall in to the trap of what people say, Lupita.
Juliana's happiness is more important than anything, for God sake.
I don't care what people say..
What really worries me is that,
People who fall in love with the same sex...
What?
I don't think they're ever happy.
Stop talking nonsense, that's not true, for God sake.
I know same sex couples who live happily.
No.
A normal life, yes. You're old-fashioned.
That's what you are.
No, I'm not old-fashioned, no.
I can't wrap my head around it.
Well, you have to read about...
I'm sorry that you had to find out that way.
I understand that you can't fully understand it.
It took me a while, too.
But I won't put my feelings aside, much less to please someone else.
So I've already made my decision to live alone.