So now, you're leaving home as if I did something wrong, no?
The only one who did something wrong here is you.
I did nothing wrong, okay?
I know what I feel and I'll continue to do it whether you like it or not.
But what did that girl do to convince you to do something like that?
What are you talking about? Why do you keep saying this stupidity?
She didn't do anything. Nobody planned it.
It just happened, okay?
Well, you're not leaving.
No?
Are you going to accept me as I am?
You're my daughter.
Of course I accept you.
But I'm not going to accept you doing these indecent things, no!
Okay, that's why I'm leaving.
Because you're not going to understand.
Yeah?
And where are you going to go?
Are you going to sleep on the street?
I don't care where. I don't care.
No.
No, you want to leave to be with her.
Hey, hey what's wrong with you?
Lupita, Lupita.
Lupita, please. Calm down.
Come with me.
Come, please.
Come.
Hey guys, sorry to interrupt, but
There's a serious problem with Guille.
What happened?
No, I think there's been some confusion, but...
The police arrested him.
What for?
Yes, yes, I don't know what for, that's what I'm going to find out.
No, I'm coming with you.
No, Valentina, you need to stay here.
No, Eva..
Vale, stop..
I can call my dad, he's a lawyer and he can help...
No, do what you want. I'll call if something happens, okay?
Should I call?
No, yeah, obviously.
Of course.
Thank you.
Wait for me. Eva.
Vale, wait.