What is happening to Juliana is normal and can happen to anyone.
What do you know about this?
Okay...
Believe it or not, I've read about this subject.
And it says that homosexuality had existed since the beginning of humanity.
For years.
So have wars,
And it's not okay to go out and kill.
This is not what I want for my daughter's future.
She's had enough already with the father she had.
The last thing she needs is for people to call her a...
Ah, hey, Lupita!
Calm down.
Take my advice.
Please put your prejudices aside.
They only exist to repress people's happiness.
No Panchito.
This can ruin my daughter's life.
How do you know that? What do you know about..
More than you.
I'm her mother.
Yeah...
Well, I hope you open your mind..
Before you hurt her and push her away.
Why did you do this to me?
What the hell did I do wrong? Where did I fail?
And don't even think I'm going to let you ruin your life.
Now with more reason, we're leaving the city.
And another thing, we're leaving this house immediately because I don't want to owe anything to that girl.
Much less, she keeps dazzling you with her money.