Quickly!
Over there.
Rogelio, go see what that was now, go.
Servando, please they have nothing to do with this. Leave them alone.
You don't get to call the shots, do you hear me?
Its me that you want.
Take me, we will leave.
Lucia, don't do this.
Shut up, sit down. Sit down.
Enough!
Go with the lady and bring me the best tequila in the house.
Servando, there is shooting out there, the police will be here soon.
Did you not hear me?
I want you to prepare food.
And bring me the best tequila in this house.
This afternoon is very promising.
Isn't that right, my lady?
Are you listening? Let's go.
Let's go!
I'm sorry Valentina, you should not be going through this.
I will do everything to make this okay.
I promise.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.