So important was the party that you had to lie to your dad.
They conviced me to and I didn't even want to go.
Really and now see how you're mad at me.
Forgive me.
Really please forgive me. I'm never doing it again.
I promise you, I'm never doing it again.
I need you to do two things to forgive you.
Well three
Ok yes, whatever you want
Really, I...
First
Promise me that you never leave the house like that.
I promise
The second one?
Tell me how you did it to leave without being seen by security.
No
Please no
Because you're gonna get mad at me again. And no I... no
No, I'm not going to get mad
No, you're going to get mad
No, I'm not going to get mad at you
And I want you to tell me because...
Maybe one day, I too need leave the house like that
You promise you're are not going to get mad.
It's going to be our secret
Ok
See the tennis court
And there is a wall
a little one
You have to stick to the wall and then crouch.
Ans then there is a blind spot for the security cameras, so there you go out.
Of course
And the third thing?
Come give me a kiss.
Thank you love.
Good thing you're fine.
I'm sorry.