Who were you talking to when I arrived?
With Panchito.
He was telling me what's going on at Milagros's house.
Ahh, poor guy, I can imagine.
Yeah.
Honestly, I feel more comfortable here.
Of course, me too.
Hey ma?
I was thinking and you're right.
I think... It might be good idea to leave the city,
or the country.
I'm not going to the USA.
No, I wasn't thinking about the USA.
I was thinking about Costa Rica.
Costa Rica?
Where is that?
In Central America.
A friend told me where we could find work and food.
Somewhere to stay.
And when did you change your mind?
No, look ma, I thought about it and you are right.
Being here is really dangerous for us.
Did something happen and you don't want to tell me?
Ma..
Look, nothing has to happen for me to want to protect my family.
Look.
Look at these photos of Costa Rica.
Honestly, its really cool.