Drink it.
And try to calm down.
Send your men.
Let them do what they need to do.
If Armenta wants to kill Lucia, I don't care.
But Valentina needs get out of there safe and sound.
- What you're saying doesn't make sense.
- Oh, no?
So what? I'm supposed to let them do whatever they want to my sister?
Calm down.
You're not thinking straight.
In a confrontation like this
I can't guarantee anyone's life, not even your sister's.
Besides,
Think.
What will the police think? And your moron husband?
But it's you that--
That the Sierra's Cartel protects your family. That's what you want them to think?
Besides!
From there until they find out about our business is one step away.
So what? I'll just sit here with my arms crossed,
While they do something to my sister? No!
I have to do something.
You're not going anywhere.
There is nothing you can do there.
You're safe here.
Is that clear?
I don't want anyone to interrupt me while I'm in the room with Lucia.
Stop with the games, Servando. We have to get out of here!
I'm the one who gives the orders here!
Understand it!
No!
No, not her. Not her!
Quickly!
Five minutes.
Give me five minutes.
What's happening?
- What's happening?
- It's okay, just relax.