Don't you think you're exaggerating a little, Servando?
It's funny that you're the one making this comment, my lady.
If you're referring to last nights call..
allow me to offer an apology,
that wasn't the correct tone to talk to you in.
How people change when they are scared, right Servando?
Talk to me and we can make an agreement.
Valentina and Silvina have nothing to do with this.
Let us talk like civilised people.
Who told you that I was a civilised person?
I can appear to be one, when something interests me.
But when a woman like you snubs me..
then I lose interest.
And I become very obsessive.
Please, please don't hurt us!
Shut up!
Unless you want to be the second person to say hello to Juanita. (his gun?)
Servando, please.
Are you going to kill three women in their own house?
And look like a coward in front of the whole world?
I think we're understanding each other, my lady.