- Okay, that's it.
- What?
- Where are you taking me?
- It's a surprise, I can't tell you.
If I tell you, it won't be surprise.
But what surprise? Well, then tell me why you dressed me like this.
Stop.
Why did I dress you this way? You choose your outfit.
What?
It's super cool. Did you not like it?
No, yeah, of course I like it.
Dude, I think we're wasting our time.
If Valentina was dating the driver, like you say, it would be him driving her, not this old guy.
- Unless she's dating the old guy.
- Look, dude, I'm sure they're doing this to mislead us.
I'm assuming they meet outside the house and that Juliana helps them.
Oh, dude, you even made up your own soap opera and everything.
- Fine, believe me or not, we're about to find out and that's it.
- All right, all right.