I'm sorry, Jacobo. I feel like I'm always crying.
I swear my life is not like this. Well, it didn't use to be, but lately...
Perhaps we are all going through the same thing today.
It's just that--
I don't want to hurt anyone, I swear it, I don't--
Vale.
Hey.
Can I give you an advice?
Try to breathe.
And to take your time.
And try to think about what it is that's really happening to you.
And do the right thing.
It's just that it's very hard to know what is the right thing, because--
The right thing to me or the right thing to the others?
- Because it seems like they're not the same, you know?
- The only thing I ask you is to try to--
Act with honesty.
I think that what matters is that you be honest with him and with yourself.
You say that because of Lucho?
I'll talk to you as if I--
As if I was-- Well--
As a man, and if I was your--
As if you were my daughter.
Don't break his heart.
I mean, try to-- Try to understand that it's a human being we're talking about, a person.
And that maybe he's in love, just like you are.
So the only thing I ask you is to understand him
And to really be honest, because there's also a person on the other side.
Jacobo,
Are you-- Are you all right?
I'm always so involved with my dramas and my weird world that I end up forgetting about other people.
Are you all right? You can tell me anything, Jacobo, okay?
What is it?
Nothing.
Nothing. I--
I appreciate it, but--
I don't even know I'm like this. I'm okay, but thank you anyway.
Thank you for worrying.
Jacobo,
I don't know what's up, but
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you.
Thank you. Honestly, thank you.
The driver?!
All this?
- All this because of the damn driver?
- That's enough.
I made you a question.
- That's who you're cheating on me with?!
- Shut up now! Now!
What is going on here?
Tell her.
Come on, tell her. Or I'll do it!