Come on, stop drinking, Lucho.
What the hell are we doing here, Lucho? We have exams tomorrow.
- Let's go.
- Dude! Wait!
I'm sure the guy Valentina is seeing won't take too long.
Yes. And how can you know?
Because obviously she told him we broke up and he will want to comfort her.
- You know what, dude? I have to go, I need to study--
- Hey, hey, hey!
Let's go, dude! I need to study!
Back me up here, don't be a bad friend.
Bad friend? Really?
Dude, we've been following your girl for hours!
I can't feel my legs, I need to go to the bathroom and you call me a bad friend?
- Great. Cool.
- I would do the same for you.
So we're not leaving.
Juliana?
- Yeah?
- You got a text message.
I'm coming. Thanks.
Thanks.
[VALENTINA: I can't stop thinking about you.]
What?
Did you read this?
No. No, of course not.
Now what happened to her?
Well, I don't know. She got a text on her phone, I told her and--
She thought I read it?
- Maybe she's seeing someone.
- No.
I would know. She tells me everything.
Oh, Lupita.
I'll tell you something.
We all have secrets.
Even you.
You have a secret behind those eyes that you don't wanna tell me.