Hey.
Did you hear about what happened?
Another murder by the narcs... For a change.
Do you think it's the same people that killed dad?
I don't know.
Who are you texting like this?
Renata, but she's not answering.
But she's okay? Did something happened to her?
No.
Eva found out about my relationship with Renata.
Mayela told her.
And so you can imagine.
She decided she's not my assistant anymore and transferred her to the management department.
Your sister doesn't have much sense.
Who does she thinks she is?
She thinks she's the family's matriarch?
That she can tell us what to do, who to date?
- I swear to you, everything was perfect--
- Until she found out.
That's the price of secrets in this house.
Honestly, it makes me feel really bad to think about
What will happen when Eva finds out about me.
I broke up with Lucho.
How was it?
Ugh, well--
Well, It's Lucho. He took it awfully.
You know how it is.
He acted violently. Obviously, he thinks I'm dating someone else, so he tried to force me to say it.
I'm very scared to think that--
All the outside things could ruin a relationship that is just beginning, you know?
And that's our problem.
That we allow
- Other people to interfere in our lives, you see?
- Always did it.
I mean, Eva trying to control us,
Lucho getting mad at you. I mean--
Do whatever you want. If you want to be with Juliana and that makes you happy,
Do it.
Me too. If i want to be with Renata, then that's it.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- So, what?
- They manipulate us. That's--
- Uh-huh. Exactly.
I'm happy that you made this decision, honestly.
We're good. You and I, we're good. Here.
Everything's fine.