I won't let you treat me like this.
I knew you were cheating on me. Tell me who it is.
- Tell me who it is!
- What? What are you talking about?
Who are you cheating on me with?!
- What's wrong with you? You're hurting me.
- And you think you're not hurting me?
- Lucho!
- Lucho, let me go.
I did everything you asked me. I was the perfect boyfriend!
- Who are you sleeping with?!
- You're drunk, stop!
- Get out of here!
- And who are you?!
- Out of here, now!
- I won't go until she tells me--
- Stop yelling and get out!
- Who are you sleeping with?
- Please, please!
- You will regret it, Valentina.
You'll regret it!
Are you all right, my love? How are you feeling?
- Silvina, give that boy some coffee, please.
- Yes.
Hey, hey. Calm down. Look at me.
- You're okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Honey,
Do you remember when I was at the hospital and you said you thought you had seen Chino?
Mom, I didn't see him, I imagined him. You said it yourself.
No, right, but--
I was all like... Confused.
How was it?
Um... I went into the cafeteria and--
Chino was there ordering coffee. I called him, but he didn't listen. I followed him and
I went after him,
But couldn't find him anymore. I dunno.
What? Don't tell me you want to go look for him.
No, no, no. It's not that.
Do you believe in that story he told us
At that hotel in San Antonio, after the hurricane?
What story?
That one, that he wasn't Chino. That he was someone else.
Ugh, mom, I don't know. That was very weird.
What I think is that Chino wanted to get rid of us and start a new life.
Do you think that's possible?
I mean--
That someone dies and then ends up inside someone else's body?
Mom, of course not.
That's bullshit. Chino was obviously nuts because of all the things he got himself into, and then
Because of the electrocution.
So you--
You don't think anything happens after we die?
Valentina is actually reading a book about that.
Oh, yeah?
But I think she's reading it hoping it'll help her overcome all the things that happened to her father.
I think that-- When you die, you die. Right?