Will you keep staring at me?
You're leaving me for the driver?
Why do you think that?
You didn't see them hugging? Comforting each other lovingly.
He's my friend, okay?
So now you're friends with the help and you even hug them, huh?
Hey, hey, hey.
Why don't you calm down and let Jacobo explain what's happening, please?
I will give you an advice so you better
Listen to it carefully.
You should be a little more respectful to someone who loved you.
That speaks very badly of you.
Understood?
Everything okay?
Tiberio, it's with you.
I think you better go, Lucho.
I can't believe it, Valentina.
You're fooling around with the driver?
You're stooping so low.
You'll pay for it.
You will pay for it.
Tiberio, go with him.