You always smell so good, how do you do it?
And your skin, it's so soft!
You're okay?
I'm nervous.
Me too.
Do you want--?
- Do you want us to-- Stop?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- No, I don't. I don't want us to stop.
Me neither. So...
This is the perfect moment to really know how we feel.
Come on, I have an idea.
My girl?
- Can I come in?
- Go away, Chivis!
- Are you having breakfast here?
- No!
- Just a juice?
- Go! Not right now.
All right. I'll wait.
Sorry.
I don't know what came into her today.
What?
What, what?
I feel weird.
Me too.
But, hey, I suppose it's normal, right?
It was the first time we did something like that.
Yes.
- Val.
- What?
I think I better go.
No, don't go.
- Val, what if someone comes in?
- No, no one is coming in.
Stay with me, please.
You know what? I'll ask Silvina to make us some "chilaquiles", she makes them super good.
And green juice.
Good morning.
Where's everyone else?
The spider's left already.
I think Guille did too and Valentina is upstairs, in her room.
It's Eva.
You know what?
- Let's go somewhere else, it's better. Yeah?
- Yes, yes.