They shot him in broad daylight.
I mean, it's--
It's been too many murders involving my family. I'm in panic. I don't know what to do.
No, Val, calm down.
Hey, look. There's a bunch of bodyguards all around you house. Nothing will happen.
Ugh! I just can't relax. Plus,
Lucho... He made a scene because he was drunk and
He thinks I'm dating the driver. Please!
What?
You mean like, Alirio?
- No, Jacobo.
- Regardless, I mean, why would he think that?
Well, I don't know. He's crazy.
I mean, I was feeling down and Jacobo gave me a hug and he literally understood everything wrong.
Juls, honestly,
Ever since my father died I haven't had a moment to breathe.
I just haven't.
No, Val, calm down.
Hey.
I don't like it when you're like that.
I would love to be with you.
But I can't leave my mother alone.
I know.
Listen.
I think--
There's someone at the door.
- I'll call you later.
- Hey. Take care, okay?
Yeah. Bye.
Hey.
It's cold.
How are you?
Panchito is there. At the house, so I was able to escape.
I honestly could only think about seeing you so
Thank you for coming.
Let's go upstairs? Yeah?
Let's go.