The house is really beautiful.
Yeah, it is very cozy.
The sunlight is very nice. It's...
It's a very peaceful place.
I mean, it still needs a couple of supplies, but Silvina will pack some things up.
And I'll bring them later.
Come on, I'll show it to you.
I don't have enough words to thank you both
For everything you've done for me.
There's no need.
Careful.
If you need anything, let me know and I'll bring it to you.
No, no, no. You've done enough. Please.
- Honestly, it's not a problem. Juls, we could--
- Huh?
Wanna go to the supermarket? We can buy the basics.
No, please, you've done so much already.
It's nothing, really.
Yeah, that's good. Would it be a problem if I left you with my my mom?
No, not at all. It's okay, go with her.
We'll be right back.
Let's go over there.
- How big!
- Yeah, I know.
Look at that.
That table... Like, how much can we eat on it?
A lot.
Where's the kitchen?
I think that's all, right?
But where's the toothpastes? And the toiletries? Is it there?
Oh, they were probably left up there.
Miss Valentina, I can go get them if you want.
Wait for me in the car, please.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- How weird, right?
- Yeah, I don't know where--
Seriously, I cannot
- Remember where I left it.
- I've no idea.
So weird.
Hey, Val.
Thanks for the house, really.
I don't even know how to thank you.
No, you don't have to thank me.
I also did it for myself.
I wanted to keep you close.
But you do know we can't stay there forever, don't you?
Maybe you can?
I mean, your mom loved the house. Did you see how she was? She was super excited.
No, Val.
When my mom feels better, she will want to leave this town.
Don't be like this.
Mmm?
Well...
I guess I'd rather you be away
But safe.
Which doesn't mean it doesn't hurt.