Here's the bag, Miss.
Should we head to Tiberio and Silvina's house?
Yeah, we're making a pit stop first.
All right.
We weren't going to stop, were we?
I didn't want to stop.
Did you want to stop?
So?
What are we going to do?
Well, I don't know.
I have no idea.
I'm having a hard time thinking of myself as gay, to be honest.
I'm also having a hard time thinking of myself as gay.
So?
Look.
What I can tell you is that
I've never felt this way about a boy.
That's a fact.
Not even Lucho?
Zero.
It's just--
You know what's the problem with you? It's that--
I can't stop thinking about you. It's like a
Broken record on a loop. It's embarrassing!
I can't stop thinking about you either.
We're in love.
With a woman?
Val.
I'm in love with you.
So what are we going to do?
Lucho.
I should have ended this a long time ago. That's the truth.
It's perfect timing, 'cause right when--
Poor thing, he has been trying.
Yeah, the truth is
He has been very nice the last few days.
He went to the hospital, donated blood.
I don't know what I'm going to tell him, poor guy.
Hey, Val, listen to me.
This is something no one should judge.
Okay?
It's something only you and I understand.
And that's fine.