My daughter, how did it go?
I'll go see what happened.
Yes, yes.
How did it go with Valentina?
I didn't go to see Valentina.
I went to see my dad at the hospital.
He says his name is Jacobo.
You're so stubborn Juliana, stop.
No, mom.
You know, he lied to my face again.
Look.
I was his woman.
I've known him intimately in the worst moments and..
I'm telling you, the man in the hospital is not him.
A person can't change so much in so little time.
Look, mom..
That's what criminals do.
That same thing again.
The same thing again?
I'm gonna tell you something.
If you want to believe his stories about souls and stuff, then that's your problem.
I'm not going to be convinced.
Okay?
If you want to be fooled, that's your problem.
He won't do that to me.