Hey.
Val, what's up? You finally answer me.
I was so worried about you.
Did you hear about what happened?
Yes. When we were talking,
Well, when I called you,
The call was still going and I saw that they were threatening you.
I rushed to your house but the police didn't let me in.
I had no idea you had been here.
Yeah.
But I heard that everyone was all right, your family and all.
And I knew they wouldn't let me in, so
I came back home. But you have no idea how relived I am to know that you're okay.
- How do you feel?
- I still can't believe that I got out of it alive.
I don't-- I don't know.
Val, I get it.
I imagine it was all really hard.
Do you want me to go to your house tomorrow?
I think it's better if I let you know when I feel better, because like--
Not yet.
I'm not in the mood to do anything.