Look, Juliana.
Don't you think that if we had a long conversation, you could realize--
I mean, I would love to tell you that I'm your father.
But I'm not Chino Valdes.
I only want to know what you were doing in the Carvajal's house.
What? Did the narcos sent you?
- Who do you have to kill?
- I don't have to kill anyone.
I am not your father.
I was defending that family, that's all.
- Why?
- Because I'm a human being and if you see someone about to kill a person
Evidently, it's logical that you do something about it.
You are Chino Valdes' daughter. Do you think that if they sent your father to kill someone
That's how he would have done it?
Wouldn't he have known how to escape? Would he have taken so long? For God sake!
Look, why don't you just speak clearly at once?
Are you or are you not my father?
I know this is complicated!
Hey, I'm sorry.
I need you to try and understand me.
And not to tell a word about this, that's all.
I assure you that I'm going to explain everything to you.
I need you to pay attention.
Juliana.
I'm sorry, Miss, but you can't be here.
- The patient needs to rest.
- Wait a minute, I'm talking to her! She'll leave after.
- Please.
- Please, get out.
- Juliana!
- Relax.
- Lay back, stay calm.
- Juliana!
- Hey!
- Calm down.