Juliana, I'm not who you believe I am.
I assure you I know perfectly who you are.
You are a liar.
When are you going to stop lying?
You hurt someone
- Who I really care about.
- I ask you to give me the opportunity to explain to you what's going on.
- It's weird but if you--
- Sure, what are you going--? What?
You want to do to me what you did to my mom, right? See if I could be fooled too.
What are you going to tell me to convince me?
I want to tell you that I'm not your father.
I mean, I'm not Chino Valdes. I'm a businessman. A 60 year old man,
With a family, with a past,
With another face, with another life, that unfortunately transmigrated or reincarnated,
However you want to call it, in the body of your father, Chino Valdes.
Just like
- Magic?
- I don't know if it was magic or what it was. I don't know!
I know that your father died in the electric chair at the same time I did!
And unfortunately I inherited everything! I mean, all the bad things! I got them all!
Okay, so--
What about the hurricane?
You didn't notice anything wrong during the hurricane?
I mean, beyond the physical appearance, didn't you feel that I was another person? Didn't--?
No, I can't believe
That you'll keep lying like that.
No, I can't believe it.
You're a liar.
You have always been a liar.