Chivis, it's to be expected that Vale doesn't want to get out of her room.
After all what happened yesterday?
My dear Eva,
My girl Valentina is in a really bad state.
- She doesn't want to eat.
- I know, the poor thing is in shock.
Why don't you give her some pills? Mmm?
So she can sleep and she'll feel better tomorrow.
Yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
If they want blood, I'll give them the blood of the princess.
You two calm down. Calm down.
Right?
No...!
- Valentina, what's happening?
- I can't do it.
Val, are you all right?
What is it?
I'm scared, Eva, I'm so scared.
I'm afraid that they'll come back.
And what are we gonna do? What are we gonna do if they come back?
What are we gonna do?