- They told me you had a bad night.
I want to offer you an apology, personally.
- You don't have to apologize. It wasn't your fault.
- Yes.
- No, you couldn't have known
That guy was going to become obsessed with you.
- But I’m responsible.
There's something I need to discuss with you.
It's about your friend Juliana.
- What about Juliana?
- Did you know she's Jacobo's daughter?
- Sorry, I didn't understand. What?
- Jacobo, the driver.
He's Juliana's, your friend's, dad.
- No.
- I imagine you didn't know, due to your reaction.
- It's just, it can't be.
I mean,
I don't know who lied to you, but, no.
- What did she tell you about her dad?
- Nothing.
Nothing good, honestly.
I mean, she hasn't seen him for a long time
And, besides,
He's a very bad person, as far as I know.
- I don't understand.
If she claims to be your friend, why did she lie to you?
- It's just, I don't know where you're getting your information but it can't be true,
Okay?
- Okay...
- You're really confusing me.