Why did you do this to me?
What the hell did I do wrong? Where did I fail?
This isn't your fault. This isn't about you, okay?
It isn't anyone's fault.
I didn't know that I was going to fall in love with a woman either.
You don't know what you are saying.
I do know what I'm saying.
I've never fell in love with anyone...
And it turns out that the first human being I fall in love with, happens to be a woman.
So what!
Can’t you understand that?
No.
And don't even think that I'm going to let you ruin your life.
So now with more reason, we are leaving the city.
And another thing, we are leaving this house immediately because I don't want to owe that girl anything.
Much less, she keeps dazzling you with her money.
You know I'm not an idiot, right?
I'm not dazzled by anyone's money.
And I'll tell you one thing...
I’m in love with Valentina and that is not going to change because you said so.
Hello.
Here.
They were kissing, Panchito.
I saw them, they were kissing
You were right.
Juliana had a secret.
And that secret was Valentina.
And?
"And"?
Yes, and?
Do you think this is normal?
Well, yes.
I don't see anything wrong with her and her friend falling in love.
You're saying that, too? Now I'm the crazy one?
Lupita, please, calm down.
Don’t make a big deal about this.