You want with or without butter?
Um, with.
Yes? Are you sure?
Here, take both.
Do I look hungry?
Yes.
So, are you going to believe?
If you keep giving me those nice arguments you were giving me,
I'm going to believe.
But
It's a lot of information, Val, it's not like..
Well, I'm not ruling out reincarnation,
But...
It's a lot of information.
Wait a moment.
Did I hear right? I'm not ruling out reincarnation?
Wait, stop what you're doing, I need you to concentrate.
Because evidently the idea isn't clear to you.
You can't leave me alone on this.
In what?
In this, in this absurd belief.
What will people think of me if you don't believe? What will they say?
That you're crazy, obviously.
You're so crazy.
How mean.
Why?
Sorry, I'm sorry.
It's a bit difficult, this whole transition.