You have to know who Jacobo is, right? I mean..
Who is he?
Valentina, Jacobo is a..
He is a great friend of mine from university, he is someone really..
I'm really fond of. He is a very, very good, kind person.
Okay... Well..
I’m sorry to say, but all of what you are saying is very complicated and
See, if this transmigration was a real thing,
Everyone would know.
People would be talking about it, it would be on the news.
Totally.
Totally, you're right. You're completely right, it's..
It happens that the topic of transmigration is not well known in the west.
It has to do with other cultures, like Tibetan, millenary cultures.
No, I'm sorry, I don't want to offend you,
But it seems like you took all of this from a movie or something.
Yes, you're right. Of course, logically is to believe or not believe, to see or not believe.
I agree with you.
I completely agree with you, that what happens here.. There was a patient..
That patient,
Appeared with a regression and themes of... reincarnation and transmigration.
What's important is that, I had to consult with my colleagues on all of this.
We investigated and..
We found that death...
Doesn't end.
Death transforms.
Yes?