Hello, Silvina.
Good morning.
Guille.
How are you, little sister?
Better.
Do you have a second? I just found out something very important.
What happened?
It turns out that Jacobo is Juliana's dad.
Juliana, your friend?
...Yes.
Why didn't we know before?
I don't know, they just found out too.
Juliana and her mom have been looking for him for a while, not knowing that he worked at the house.
Seriously?
That's weird.
I know, what worries me is that Juliana said her dad is a hitman.
What?
I swear.
Look, Valentina, you know what you're saying is very serious.
Are you sure?
I know, my reaction was the same.
Does Lucía know?
I don't think so.
I'm trying to find her but Chivis said she is not here, so I can't talk to her.
She's probably in the office.
I need to tell her, she needs to know.
Yes. I agree, that would be great.
It's better to do it in person so there are no misunderstandings.
Besides, we are going to go to Camilo's house because at the end of the day,
He recommended Jacobo and I want to know why he recommended a hitman.
Please let me know what he says.
Okay. Take care, okay? Tell me what happens with you, too.