No, where are you going?
Explain to me what this is.
Because I've seen you kissing.
You've been fooling me this whole time.
What did you do to my daughter?
Mom, what is wrong with you?
She didn't do anything to me.
This is ours.
I'm your mother, I know you've never done anything wrong.
This is not wrong.
Love isn't a perversion, okay?
And I'll tell you one thing.
This is the most beautiful thing I've felt in my entire life.
What love? She took advantage of you.
Mom, Mom.
Calm down.
She didn't take advantage of me.
Of course she did.
Who else knows about this?
Get out!
Mom, Mom, Mom, hey!
What do you mean "get out?"
You're going to throw her out of the house that she lent you?
Do you need something, miss?
No.