I think that..
It would be a big mistake to go to the police and turn in a man that really is..
Innocent.
Jacobo Reyes is innocent.
Okay, okay, so.. okay wait, so if..
Jacobo isn't Chino, then where is Chino's soul?
Disappeared? In another body?
Those questions don't have answers yet.
I don't have them, but I will, okay?
Okay, good, then while we wait for answers, I have to go to the hospital.
I have to talk to Jacobo because..
He is the closest thing I have to my dad.
And he can tell me how things happened.
But going there isn't safe.
He is hospitalized and he just killed a narco.
Don't go there.
No, don't go.
Yes, no.
I mean.. he has a point.
I don't know if it's safe.
When they discharge him, he is coming here and then you can come see him.
Yeah, we should do that. When he's out, you..
You'll let us know and we'll come see him.
I will, yes. Yes.
Yes.
Girls, I need you to understand something important.
Jacobo Reyes is a great friend.
A true friend.
Besides, I'm talking about an excellent human being.
A good guy.
Yes?
Camilo?
Did Jacobo know my dad?