I'm sorry to take you out of your house when you still don't feel good.
Look, I think it's better to be here than to be locked at home.
How are you feeling because I saw you..
You were a little shocked by what Camilo said.
Well..
Val, honestly, it's gonna take a bit of work for me to believe all of these..
Things, but..
Can I say something?
That book is..
Very magical.
You have to give it a chance, because if not...
Obviously, you're going to be skeptical and not to believe,
But it changed my life.
Look.
I even have it marked.
This phrase.
"Different spiritual disciplines affirm that souls reincarnate in the same family, either blood or friendship.
Think about it, it makes sense.
It does make sense.
Also, if that's true...
I could meet with my family again and..
You could have been my...
Prince Charming in another life.
Which..
Makes so much sense and would explain a lot of things, don't you realize?
Yes.
With that argument, I think...
I could start believing in these things.