How are you?
Hey.
Good?
This is Juliana.
How are you? Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
Juliana.
Ah, Juliana?
Come in, please, come in.
Go ahead, go ahead, please.
So, tell me..
How are you feeling?
Good.
I feel better with what you prescribed but that's not why we're here.
It's a long story.
Valentina...
So, what is this about?
It's about...
Jacobo Reyes.
Basically, we want to know why you're friend with a hitman.
Juliana and her mom came here to escape from Texas because,
He abandoned them with a...
A gang of narcos chasing them.
And now he appears at my home, recommended by you, becomes my driver,
And now he is saying that he's not her dad.
Which obviously is a lie,
And I don't know how many people he has been lying to, but I'm not going to let him continue.
I'm going to the police.