Look, look.
I can explain, although, it is complicated.
Juliana, no? Juliana?
Juliana.
It turns out that,
Jacobo Reyes died and reincarnated in the body of,
El Chino Valdés.
Your father.
It's absurd.
Are you serious?
I'm very serious.
Are you talking seriously?
It's complicated,
Very difficult to understand but what I'm doing is very serious.
Believe me, please, yeah?
It's absurd. It doesn't make sense, right? No..
That doesn't happen.
This has to do with what I have been practicing.
What I am studying, the migration of souls.
Yes?
What I read in your first book?
It has to do with reincarnation which is completely different to transmigration.
This is when the human dies, but he keeps the conscience of their previous life.
Juliana, if you want I could give you my first book so you can study...
Camilo, what I don't understand is, if El Chino is not Juliana's dad, then who is he?