Vale.
Please don't be impulsive.
Think things through.
What are people going to say?
I don't care what people say.
Oh really?
Yes.
And did you already tell your friends from school?
What did they tell you?
They don't know, OK? They don't know.
But they're not going to react like you
because they're not close minded like that, Evangelina.
You honestly don't know what you're doing, Vale.
I'm only going to warn you that I'm not going to allow you to insult the house of my parents.
So you tell that girl not to come back,
if you don't want me to put her in her place.
You're not going to put anyone in their place, OK?
You don't even have the right --
You know what?
Thank goodness our father isn't here.
Because if not, he'd be really disappointed --
Don't bring dad into this.
Oh, no?
No.
And what did you think he was going to do?
Applaud you?
Celebrate the news?
Look, Vale.
You know what? You got me fed up.
I know now that you're infatuated and nothing is going to change your mind.
I only hope that by tomorrow, you don't regret this.
When all your little friends turn their backs on you.
That's not going to happen.
What is going to happen, is that at the end of everything,
The one who's going to end up alone.
Is you.
That's not true, Eva.
That's not true.