Vale?
Chivis?
Yes?
- Yes, ma'am, I'm here.
- Hi, Chivis, has Valentina arrived?
- No, not yet.
- Well, when she gets home let me know, okay?
Yes. Excuse me.
Chivis.
- Yes?
- Shh.
Yes, my girl?
- Is Eva home? Hi.
- Hi.
Yes, she's in her room.
- She asked me to let her know when you arrived.
- Okay, no, no, no. Don't tell her.
Guille's here?
- Yes, he's also in his room.
- Okay.
- Don't go tell Eva I'm here.
- No.
- Where are you traveling to?
- I'm not going on a travel.
I'm moving out.
- What?
- Yes.
I want to live my life the way I want. However I feel like.
And I want to show the entire world that I'm capable of succeeding on my own and--
No, Guillermo-- Listen.
- You are really wrong. You can't move out.
- Why am I wrong?
- Because you can't go. Come on, be logical. What's the matter with you?
- Eva!
Eva. Eva! She's the problem.
I'm tired of her telling us what we should do.
Of her wanting to control us all the time.