Thank you.
I don't want to be here. I don't--
I want us to go some place where there's nobody else. That we stay there, that we can disappear.
That we don't need to come back to this damn--
Val, hey.
I don't want to be away from you either.
But I don't want to keep hiding.
What?
Are you afraid to talk to your sister?
Ugh, I'm--
This is getting too intense, to be honest.
- Val.
- What?
Hey,
- We knew it was going to be like this.
- Yeah, but I thought we were going to have more time, okay?
That I was going to be more prepared. That--
Hey, relax! Listen to me.
When you're with your sister, remember the pact.
Everything's going to be okay.
Calm down.
No, I know, but it's just too much.
I can't take it anymore.
What happened, honey?
Weren't you going to spend the whole day with Valentina?
We came back earlier.
Juliana, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Give her some space.
It'll pass.