Listen to me.
Look.
I know that the death of our dad affected you.
It hurt all of us.
And it hurts everyone differently.
That's why I know that this confusion that you're having,
these feelings that you think you have,
for this girl,
is only a product of the depression that you're living.
This has nothing to do with any depression.
I like Juliana.
I'm in love with Juliana.
I'm in love with her.
I can't believe what's happening to me.
It's cause this isn't happening to you.
It's happening to me, Eva.
But you are my sister and you are a Carvajal!
And I'm not going to give you permission to have this relationship.
So, tell that Juliana,
that she can't come to this house,
nor the Valle house,
nor any property of the family.
Do you understand?
Answer me! Do you understand?
You being the older sister
doesn't give you the right
to tell me what to do.
Not me, nor Guille, OK?
Do you not realize what's happening?
Guille left the company. He left the house.
You want me to leave too?
You're going to end up alone, Eva.
Alone, Eva.
- You're going to end up alone.
- Vale.