Enough.
I can't anymore.
Do you know what she did to me?
What did she do? What did she do?
She found out I was dating Renata
and she decided she's not my secretary.
She moved her to another department.
I did go talk to her, and I asked her nicely
that she put her back to position.
And she didn't care.
What are you going to do?
Quit.
What?
Renata did the same. I mean enough, enough.
We're going to start from zero.
And I thought my life was complicated.
What do you mean complicated?
What happened?
Lucho caught me and Juliana in the Valle house.
And obviously he told Eva.
And what did she say?
I don't know. I have no idea.
Obviously I haven't gone to see her.
It gives me panic.
That's what Eva needs to understand.
That everyone
can live their life how they want.
You understand?
And you, Val, need to look into your heart
and need to find what makes you happy.
You shouldn't care about what she thinks --
what the world thinks.
You understand?
Look, Guille.
Look, I --
I understand, OK?
And I love you, and I support you.
But you can't leave me like this.
Please, no.
I'm sorry, Val.
It's - It's already decided.
It's not the same without you.
Please.