Come in.
I'm here. What do you want?
Lucho came to see me at my office.
And he told me something I hope isn't true.
Well, I don't know what he told you, but yes either way.
Valentina, are you crazy?
You don't like women.
No.
I like Juliana.
Vale.
Don't say those things.
You've had boyfriends all your life.
I've known you forever.
You are not homosexual.
Also, where did Juliana come from?
Who introduced you to her?
What does that have to do with this?
Because I'm sure she got close to you because of your interest.
That is not true, OK?
And you haven't even tried with her.
You have no reason to say something like that.
Val, it's because you are so naive.
I'm naive? I'm naive?
No!