You need to understand that everything is happening is not real and also there...
There are professional ways of making it  disappear.
You also think I'm crazy.
I swear...
I feel like they will appear at any time and...
I...
I just want to turn off what I'm feeling, I don't care how.
I believe you.
I'm a professional, I see many patients and this happens, yes.
I understand you perfectly and I believe you.
So...
You can make me stop feeling this?
It can be done professionally. If you would like, we could do hypnosis.
No.
Yes.
I want something easier.
Okay.
I want to leave this behind. I don't want to think anymore.
Well...
We can do something easier.
I could give you a prescription, you could take a few pills.
They will calm you.
And when you want to, if you want to, we can do the hypnosis. What do you think?
I want you to know that Eva will be looking after you.
You're the closest thing I have to a father.
Thank you.