No, everything I'm telling you, I saw it on the news.
Poor Valentina, dude.
Imagine..
They come into your house and hold you hostage.
Do you really not want to know how she is?
If she's okay or want to see her?
And why me?
I don't matter to her, let her girl go see her.
Dude, grow up. What are you, 2?
Stop with that, no? You made everyone turned their back on her.
Even Claudio and Piña who are also gays.
What is that?
They supported me because they wanted to. I didn't pull a gun on them.
Well, let me tell you, they looked stupid with their homophobic comments. You need to stop.
- Look, Sergio, I'm not homophobic.
- It doesn't look like...
But, Valentina wasn't fair with me. She wasn't honest and she deserved a little bullying, that's it.
Let me tell you that she has suffered enough, okay?
And now with this, a lot more.
Imagine narcos coming into your house.
Don't you feel sorry for her at all?
Look.
I'm really happy to know she is fine, but that's it.
I don't want to see her again.
She has someone to comfort her, she doesn't need me.
But no, she doesn't have anyone to comfort her. If you're talking about Juliana, they're over.
I spoke to her not long ago and she said they have broken up. She wants to leave the country with her mom.
Get with it, okay!