Val, I thought that I would never see him again.
It makes no sense...
It doesn’t make any sense because you said the person who is your dad, is a hitman, okay?
And Jacobo...
Is a beautiful person who works in this house and saved my life.
Who.. Who talks to me.
It has nothing to do – no, you know what, I don’t know what to believe.
- You better leave, Juliana.
- No, you have to listen to me, Val.
I’ll leave later if you want me to. Listen.
I went to look for my dad at the hospital
To ask him what he has been doing here.
You know what he said to me?
That he's not my dad.
Seriously...
- I know.
- What is that supposed to mean?
I dont understand.
- You would understand that.
- Yes.
It doesn’t make any sense.
I dont know how to explain this to you.
He told me that
He is someone who died and
And that he woke up on my dad’s body.
No...
I already know that it's crazy.
I don't believe it either.
The problem is that my mom does.
My mom believes that Jacobo is not El Chino.
What do you think?
I think...
There is someone we should see.