Thank you, Chivis.
Here, my love.
When I was mugged in New York, I took pills for like 2 months.
I'm telling you this..
I'm telling you so you know that after a little while, you won't get scared and you won't even remember it.
You know what is super helpful?
What?
Company.
If you want, I can come by after work...
Make you some dinner,
We can watch a movie..
Really, that isn't necessary, but thank you.
Well..
I know it isn't necessary, besides, it’s not a problem.
I've missed you a lot.
I love being here, hanging out with you.
With both of you.
I do think that you should organize something.
I don't want to do anything, to be honest.
To distract yourself for a while.
Why not...
A dinner, with Lucas?
It's..
Her boyfriend.
What Lucas?
Lucas, Lucas?
Lucas. Do you remember Lucas?
How funny. I’m glad that you are finally together.
Yes.
If you want, I will ask Lucas and we can plan something fun.
Okay.