How are you?
Good.
You?
I'm so glad to see you.
Here, sit.
What happened at the house was..
Very intense honestly, but...
I don't want to talk about that.
I asked you here for another reason.
I'm going to ask you a question.
And I want you to be really honest with me.
Okay?
Is Jacobo your dad?
Yes.
I can't believe you lied to me like that. I thought...
No.
I thought we could trust each other.
Were you lying the whole time?
No, no, no, look, Val.
You did.
No, I didn't know that my dad worked here.
How did you not know your dad worked here?
Val, I've never seen him here.
The first time I saw him here was after the kidnapping.
When the police brought him out, when they put him in the ambulance.
Val, I never lied to you.
I don't have a reason to lie. I've never lied to you.