- What are you doing here?
- Why do you care?
- You've got nothing to do here.
- Look, I'm already going.
But not because you asked me to but because it's best.
So they don't see us fighting.
- Vale,
are you okay?
Take this, I brought you water.
- I don't want it--
- Valentina...
- Eva, don't...
- I brought you some painkillers, you're going to take them.
- I'm not going to take any painkillers.
- Come on, you're very upset.
- I'm not upset!
- Give me your hand.
- Stop, Eva!
- I've thought about it.
I'm going to report El Chino.
- What are you saying?
- He's a criminal.
He can't be free, with another identity,
and go unnoticed.
- Well, on the radio they're saying he's the one who saved
The Carvajal family by killing that narc.
- Ah! And you believe it? Really?
Come on, El Chino is a liar, eh?
He convinced you that he's another man. I mean...
- Juliana, please.
Don't report him to the police.
Wait until you find out a bit more about him.
- What else do you want me to find out?
I don't understand why you keep defending that man. What's up?
Are you still in love with that trash?
After all the things he's done to you?
Come on,
I'm not like you.
- Please...
Don't do it.