Don't pressure her.
Nobody is pressuring her.
Just that, this was already too much, Camilo.
Valentina has been depressed and doing silly things for a long time.
I think you should medicate her.
Eva, listen. She needs family protection.
Family support.
Valentina is always surrounded by people.
There are always lots of people in the house.
Yes, there are always people in the house.
I remember perfectly, this house is always full.
But, who's listening to her?
No one.
It's like your father. Do not make the same mistake your father did.
Did he listen? No, he listened to absolutely no one.
And that is what you should not do. Understand?
How are you?
I'm very good, thank you.
Yes?
Yes.
You know, my house is always open to you, when you want to talk.
Yes, thank you so much, Camilo.
I will come see you when I can.
You will?
Yes.
Listen to Valentina, okay?
Bye.