This man has your father's body but he's not Chino.
His name is Jacobo Reyes.
- How do you know that?
- Because he told me.
He came to bring me the things that Mrs. Silvina sent us when we moved here.
We were both surprised.
It's just that-- It's just, no--
None of these things you're telling me make sense.
No, it didn't make sense to me either. He had to try really hard to convince me that he wasn't your father.
And why didn't you tell me?
Because he asked me not to. He said that if I told you, it could complicate things.
It's just that--
And if he's not Chino, then who is he?
I already told you.
His name is Jacobo Reyes, that's all I know.
But he was very nice to me and
I want to keep the promise of not revealing his secret.
What--?
Not revealing the secret that he is not Chino Valdes?
He's a hitman, mom.
Chino is very clever, he can make up any excuse to get into that house and do whatever he was asked to do.
But he is not your father.
Why would I lie to you?
No, not you. Him!
Please, Juliana.
Don't tell Valentina that her driver lives in your father's body.
Of course I'm not gonna tell her. She'll think I'm crazy.
Please.
Keep this secret.