Valentina, come.
Okay, take everyone to the station.
The guards too. Get the testimonies from all of them.
Detective, where is the ambulance?
Calm down, it's on its way.
It's taking too long.
What happened in here, Lucia?
Servando came back.
He held us hostage for hours, he was about to kill Valentina. If it wasn't for Jacobo,
We would be dead.
You killed... Servando Armenta?
Jacobo.
- Can't the ambulance come quicker?
- Calm down, it's coming.
Jacobo, you killed Servando Armenta?
- Apply more pressure.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
Mateo, what else has happened?
I don't know yet, I'm about to go into the house. As soon as I'm in there, I'll tell you everything.
- The police is already here.
- Tell them I'm coming there right now.
Hey, Miss, where are you going?
- You can't go in there.
- I'm a friend of Valentina's.
- Step back.
- Listen to me, please. I need to know how Valentina is.
Please, Gutierrez!
- You can't pass, it's not safe.
- Well, tell me how she is then. Is everything okay? What happened?
- Miss, you can't come in. Step back.
- All right. Okay, okay. Fine.
Can one of the paramedics help me out, please?
Don't look over there. She's having a panic attack. Please, help her.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. And you, ma'am?
- Breathe.
- I'm-- I'm calm.