Servando!
Servando, we're losing! They're coming in.
- Why don't you just kill them--?
- Shut up!
I've already told you that I'm not going to leave this place before I finish what I came here to do.
Isn't that right, honey?
What are you waiting? Go! That's what I pay you for!
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Come here, princess.
- No. No, Servando!
- Shut up!
- No, no, no.
I promise you I'll do whatever you want me to.
If what they want is blood, I'll give them the blood of the princess.
You two calm down. Calm down.
Armenta!
Look at that! The super driver.
Are they paying you overtime to be a ridiculous imbecile?
How much are you worth?
- How much are you worth?!
- Let her go or I'll kill him!
Let her go!
What are you thinking, pal? I have 30 more of those.
Be careful! Valentina!
Servando, the police!
Freeze! Get on the ground, drop the gun!
To the ground!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Oh, no, no, no! Call an ambulance!
A phone, please.
An ambulance, please, somebody call one!
Please, a phone.