That's not possible.
What do you mean it's not possible?  I'm telling you, I saw him.
I saw when they got him out of Valentina's house and into the ambulance.
Ambulance?
I don't know, something happened to him. But it wasn't that bad because he was walking.
Still, I went to all of the hospitals looking for him, but I couldn't find him.
- Hey, you need to calm down.
- No, mom. How am I going to calm down?
He could've killed Valentina.
Juliana, listen to me carefully.
You couldn't find your father at the hospitals
Because Chino Valdes doesn't exist.
What?!
I'm telling you that I saw him.
No.
The man you saw works as a driver at Valentina's house.
He's not your father.