If it hadn't been for Jacobo I wouldn't be here.
Val, it's all so shocking, what you're telling us.
Please, don't think about that anymore. It's over, little sis.
- It's over.
- But it's just--
What happens if they-- If they come back?
- No, no.
- It could happen and--
- Valentina, nobody is coming back.
- They'll come for revenge.
No! Listen to me.
- Guille, we are alone in this house.
- No, Valentina, listen to me.
There are security guards in the house.
For now, you need to get rest.
Do you hear me?
Why don't you call Juliana?
That way you can distract yourself a little, watch some movies, talk.
You can disconnect from all of this.
Whatever you want.
We're not together anymore.
What happened?
Tell us.
The thing is I'm more alone than ever, to be honest.
Hey... Val.
I want you to know
That from now on you've got a friend in me, okay?
Call me
And I'll come here to be with you.
Truly.
I told you I liked her.