Eva.
We don't know anything yet.
Are those gun shots?
Yes, yes, yes! The narcs and the police are shooting.
They are all inside your house.
Please, tell them not to shoot, they could hurt someone.
Yes, yes, we know that! We know! But there's nothing we can do.
What do you know about Valentina?
I don't know anything Eva. I'll call you later.
Hey, be careful! Come here, come here!
- Careful! Come here! Cover yourself, cover yourself!
- What's happening?! What's happening?!
The narcs are in the house, we don't know what's going on.
- Stay covered, stay covered!
- No, no, no!
How? How?
I'm telling you, she's been acting weird for a while and never explains anything.
Did she say where she was going?
No, she didn't say it. She was in such a hurry and she's taking too long.
Look, relax, Lupita. She probably went out to see her boyfriend.
You'll see she'll be back soon.
Something tells me my daughter is in danger.
Valentina is in there.
- No, no, we don't know that.
- No, no! I'm telling you! Listen to me, listen to me!
I was talking to her just now, and I saw her. I swear! I saw her, she's in there! And there are two other people.
She's being kept hostage, but there isn't much we can do, calm down! There's nothing we can do.
Stay covered! Be careful.
Valentina will be okay.
Oh, no!
- No!
- Back me up, back me up!
What is this girl doing here?
Why are you here?!