Chino's daughter was there and she saw me.
- No.
- Yes, she saw when I went out. In fact, she was calling my name.
I mean, can you imagine if Valentina finds out about this? I'm screwed, Camilo.
- Here, I need you to write the date of your arrival and exit, please.
- Miss?
Yes, tell me.
- How can I find an injured man who was carried by an ambulance?
- Let's see. Name?
Macario Valdes.
There is no information from the Red Cross.
So what can I do?
Well, go check the Secretary of Health's database, it should be there.
Thank you.
I can't find my glasses. Do you know where they are?
No.
- Come, come. I can introduce you to Lucia.
- Right now?
- But it's not a good time.
- Yes, I know, but--
Lucia?
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
What’s going on, honey?
You look pale.
There was a shooting at Valentina's house.
- How is Valentina?
- No, no, no, Valentina is fine.
Her family is fine, but something worse happened.
Well, tell me. You're scaring me.
My father was there.
Chino Valdes was there and I'm sure he had something to do with it.