Everything is over. I'm here to take care of you. You're not alone.
Guille!
- Are you okay?
- Yes... I'm okay. I thought I wouldn't see you guys again.
Don't say that.
The most important thing is that you're okay.
I wish it had been me instead, to go through all of that.
It's over.
Finally Servando Armenta's obsession for Lucia
Ended up being his own downfall.
You don't know how glad I am that it's over.
And this must be a big blow to the organization?
Well, yes. With the leader being dead and the other one in jail,
Surely, they will disarticulate, but
They will quickly re-organize.
It always happens in this country.
That's why we don't let our guard down, Mateo.
But certainly this is a victory.
- Thank you all. See you.
- Thank you.