I don't know.
- Sir, stop. You can't come in, it's not safe.
- I'm the owner of this house. Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Mr Corona. I didn't recognize you at first.
- Thank you, thank you.
- No, no, wait. Wait, sir. Sir!
Sir!
I'm Valentina's friend, please let me in. Please.
- We're going to get you onto the stretcher.
- That won't be necessary.
- It's for your own good.
- I'm telling you, there's no need. I'm fine.
- Jacobo, please, don't be stubborn. Let them get you on the stretcher.
- I'm fine, okay?
Sorry.
You need to come with us to the ambulance, Sir.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
- Eh-- Are you okay?
- Yes, thank you.
That's good.
Thank you.
We were going to shoot, but we didn't dare, because they had Miss Valentina.
They came in and threatened us, took our weapons and that's when they came inside.
You were there, right, Tiberio?
Yes, when I heard the shooting, I looked over and I saw a lot of armed men.
I was very scared. The first thing I did was trying to talk to my wife so she would warn the Mrs.
But as I dialed, they surprised me and I couldn't talk to them. I thought they were going to kill me.