Valentina had been very weird with me these last days and then, out of nowhere, she broke up with me.
I guessed she was cheating on me but I never imagined it was with a woman.
- No, no, no, that can't--
- I was never that fond of this Juliana girl.
She took advantage of her, of the depression your sister was in, because of her father's death.
So she surely took advantage of it to confuse her.
Valentina is not a lesbian, I can guarantee you!
You, as her older sister, should get her away from that Juliana,
Because if this gossip gets out, it will be a mess. And you know what would happen if--
No, no, Lucho, stop! It's enough.
From now on, I will deal with it. I'll talk to her.
Totally. I'm already used to dealing with all the scandals in my family.
Thank you for coming here to tell me.
I assume that now this stays between you and me.
- Believe me when I say I don't want to tell anyone else.
- Thank you.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have a lot of things to do.
Yes.
Sorry for interrupting you. Thanks for allowing me in.
Oh, dear God. It can't be.
Val.
- Val. Val!
- What?
What?
You understand why we have to go?
Mhm-hmm.