And this house?
Welcome!
Whoa.
Who lives here?
Um...
We do.
- Well--
- It's beautiful.
For one day, but yeah. Thank you.
It's incredible.
We used to come to this house a lot when I was a girl.
Until my mom died and after that, well... We sort of stopped coming.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you for coming.
I thought that
It would be nice for us to have a little privacy, right?
This could be our secret place, if you want.
- I like it.
- You like it?
Okay.
Come, I'll show you the rest.
Dude.
I know this house. It's her family's.
I've been here.
I really doubt she came all the way here only to meet with the driver, to be honest.
No.
No one comes here anymore.
I'm sure they decided to meet here.
Valentina cheated on me.
Valentina cheated on me, dude!