Dude.
I can't believe it.
Seriously, I cannot believe it.
I mean, did you never suspected it?
Valentina isn't even a lesbian.
Well, she doesn't look like one.
I can only imagine how things will be like when people from college find out.
Don't you even think about telling them!
No one will mock me, do you hear it? No one!
I broke up with him, you know? I mean, he's my ex boyfriend.
He doesn't have any right to show up like this and
He's always been very violent, but now, I don't know, he went crazy--
- I'm sorry, okay?
- No.
I'm sorry. No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, because I know you shouldn't be going through this.
This is my fault.
No, Val, relax.
No.
You do know this is not over, don't you?
I know.
But you and I are together.
Okay?
Okay.