Calm down, don't be stupid. Let's go!
I think it must be Alirio.
I'm gonna go check.
Wait, wait. Let's go together.
Juliana-- No.
- I saw you two kissing.
- Lucho.
- You could have at least invited me, no?
- No, wait--
- I love you and this is how you repay me?
This is how you repay me?!
- Hey, relax.
- You don't understand.
- This is how you repay me?!
- Calm down.
- Shut up! All you want is to-- is to
- Fool around with my girlfriend, right?
- No, no, no!
- Hey!  What's wrong with you?! Let her go!
- I'm glad your dad died.
- Let her go! Now!
- I'm glad your dad died!
- Let her go!
- Don't hit her, she's a girl! Stop!
Let's go! Stop!
- This doesn't end here.
- Go away! Go!
- This doesn't end here!
- Let's go!
I'm not done with you two! I'm not done!
Go away!
Val, Val, calm down.
Come here, come here.
Calm down, it's okay, it's fine. They're gone.
Are you okay? I'm sorry, (my love?).
- I'm sorry, (my love?).
- Val, there's no problem. Calm down.