Why did you let Jacobo go?
What do you want me to do?
Tie his leg to the table, or what?
No, but you should have called me.
I did, you didn't answer.
Here he is.
Here.
Do you know what you've done?
Hey, nothing happened. I'm a grown man, I can look after myself, okay.
You can look after yourself?
Yes.
You know what happened with the narcos while you were gone?
Hey?
Alacran kidnapped my daughter.
What?
You know what they want?
Obviously, they want to exchange her for Chino Valdés.
You know who has Chino Valdés' body? Can you imagine or do I need to tell you?
You're not gonna turn him in to the narcos, right?
He's an important man, unlike you Beltrán.
Shut up.
Ah you weren't worried about my body? Do you want to know what's happening now or not?
You know what I've been thinking?
What?
Your doctor, or anyone
Can give my body back.
So why not you, no?
I better turn you in to Alacran.
He kills you,
Debt paid.
I'm still alive and kicking..
And can finally enjoy life.
What do you think?
Excuse me?
I'm kidding.
I wouldn't do something like that.
I'm not capable.
You won't turn him in to the narcos?
How would I do that?
How? If it was me but this man isn't me.
So how are you planning to rescue your daughter?
We'll have to wait for Alacran to show up under our noses.
Since you're here, understand it.
You're staying here.
Don't let him out.
Shackle him.
Shackles..