Stop crying, you're going to ruin my good mood.
And, believe me..
That's not good for anyone.
So let's save ourselves the games and the..
'I don't know.'
'Let me go.'
Let's get to the point.
Where is your dad?
I've already told your men, I have no idea where he is.
Listen carefully.
I will settle this debt I have with El Chino
And collect a lot of interest.
And it's better to work with me.
Believe me.
So tell me, where is your dad?
Don't you get it? I don't know where Chino is.
I don't know where Chino is. I've never know where Chino is, not even when he lived in my house.
So you're here in Mexico by chance, or what?
My patience is running out, girl.
No, my patience is running out.
You killed my mom and Chino didn't show up, understand?
You're going to kill me and be humiliated because Chino won't show up
Because he doesn't care about me, or my mother, or anyone.
Hey, be careful.
I'm not going to kill you because you're important to Chino.
I'm going to kill you for the pleasure of seeing you suffer.