It's seems like..
They are finally going out and...
I think that Juliana is starting to like men because they slept together.
Valentina, how are you?
Do you know anything about the lawyer working on Guille's case? Is there any news?
No. He's still working on the defense, I think.
But, Mayela said I can get in..
Yes.
Yeah, but I suppose only family can get in.
Hey.
You are family.
Don't worry, okay. I have..
The name of the magistrate, I'll go,
Give them the information so they can let us in.
How did you meet with El Chino so fast?
I've told you, I have my contacts.
Now, we have to exchange him for Juliana.
That man that you have isn't El Chino.
His name is Jacobo Reyes.
Oh please, you're actually convinced of this.
That man will say what he has to, to save himself.
We need to save your daughter, Juliana.
I have to..
Find a way to get the message to Alacrán.
I know how to send it.
You do?
How?
Remember, I was kidnapped at that house.
I know where it is.
That's great. That's great news, Lupita.
Well done.