Renata has been here since you were brought in.
Seriously?
I swear.
Yes, I never left.
And I wasn't allowed to see you until now.
My love, did you get the food I prepared for you?
That was you?
No wonder it was so nice.
I guess compared to what you get here, anything would be good.
It was delicious.
I swear this won't last much longer, okay?
I spoke with Eva and she's been talking to Mr Barreto,
We're going to do everything to convince Mr Castillo. I swear we will get you out of here.
Yes, my love, we're all worried about you and doing everything we possibly can.
I know.
You don't know how much I miss you.
I even miss your cat.
Tlacoyo.
We miss you so much.
Miss, that's prohibited.
Relax.
Okay, I promise that this is the last time we will meet here.
Next time we see each other, we will be eating something delicious at your house, with Tlacoyo, okay?
I promise.
My love.
Promise me one thing..
You will hold up until the end like the Carvajal you are, okay?
I promise you.