Don't dare answer the phone if you don't know the number.
Only answer if you know who it is, okay?
What happened?
Juliana was kidnapped.
What do you mean kidnapped?
It's Alacran's people.
We have to really think about what we're going to do.
If they call from Juliana's phone, the only one who answered is him. Here.
They must keep thinking that you're dead.
Another thing. It will be night soon.
We have to be patient, we can't do anything until morning, yes?
Do not go to the police or go looking for Juliana.
Who are you to tell us what to do, huh?
I don't need to give you an explanation, kid.
I'm the only one who knows how to deal with a narco.
I'm the only real opportunity we have to get the girl back.
Okay, good, if you know so much about the narco's world..
Do you have any idea how to find El Chino Valdés?
Because he's the one they're looking for.
Him.
Chino Valdés.
That's a good idea.
See you later.
Lupita.