So I'm your exchange currency to get your daughter back?
No, no, no. He's joking, right Beltrán?
You wouldn't do the same?
And what, you think I'm just going to accept your stupid plan?
Oh no.
No, no, let's calm down.
You're going to kill me?
And the pact..
You have with them?
What will happen?
Let's say that the pistol is my way of convincing you.
Are you in or out?
Put that away, for God sake.
You're making me nervous.
Don't be scared.
I have a plan.
Swap me for your daughter, yes?
Play A.
I will make them believe that I'm giving you to them and they will give Juliana back.
I'm your bait, Beltrán?
Exactly.
If everything goes well, nobody gets hurt. It's all good.
Plan B. This will worry you.
Something goes wrong,
Alacrán takes you, I take Juliana and the rest is your problem.
Good business, no?
Maybe, that's why we were destined to meet.
To pay my daughter's ransom with my own body. This one.
Are you in?
Beltrán, you have blood on your shirt.
I'm fine.
I'm going to try to find Alacrán.
You know, no games, no leaving, no wandering off.
Any nonsense and she will be the one who pays.
And you..
He doesn't leave here.
Because I swear, you'll find your house in ashes.
You know..
Nobody leaves this house.