Dude.
You outdone yourself, renting an apartment for the party?
Well done, Sergio.
Yeah.
Hey, how many rooms does it have?
It has two.
And one has a jacuzzi.
Really?
Just checking on you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you uncomfortable.
Hey, hey, I see you my man, you had action.
What a player.
You could have changed the sheets.
So who was here? Tell me.
I'm sorry, but a gentleman has no memory.
Don't be like that, surely you're writing to her...
Hey dude, give me my phone. Hey.
Don't start.
Give me my phone, dude. Now.
You've seen who it is, give it back.
Did you sleep with Juliana?
Don't say anything dude..
Wait..
Please, don't say anything.
It was just once, it won't happen again, we're friends.
Friends? Friends with benefits..
Wait, isn't she gay?
How did you do it?
Dude, please.
Dude, I'm your friend. Tell me.
Okay, yes, shut up.
You can't say nothing dude, you know how things are, shut up.
Yes.
Don't worry, I won't say a thing.
Hello.
Leave your message, I'll call you when I can.
Juls, I've been trying to get a hold of you all day.
Hey.
If you're mad or if something happened we can talk, okay, but don't get away.